Bernie	Bernie	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
or	or	CC	O	O
Elizabeth	Elizabeth	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
?	?	.	O	O
				
Be	be	VB	B-VP	O
informed	inform	VBN	I-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Compare	compare	VB	B-VP	O
them	them	PRP	O	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
issues	issue	NNS	I-NP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
matter	matter	NN	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Issue	issue	NN	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Who	who	WP	B-NP	O
makes	make	VBZ	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
dankest	dank	JJS	I-NP	O
memes	meme	NNS	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
Extending	extend	VBG	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Brexit	brexit	NN	I-NP	B-MISC
deadline	deadline	NN	I-NP	O
until	until	IN	B-PP	O
October	October	NNP	B-NP	O
31st	31st	JJ	B-AP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
order	order	NN	B-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
ensure	ensure	VB	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
deal	deal	NN	I-NP	O
everyone	everyone	NN	I-NP	O
can	can	MD	B-VP	O
agree	agree	VB	I-VP	O
with	with	IN	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Using	use	VBG	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
extension	extension	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
elect	elect	VB	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
prime	prime	JJ	I-NP	O
minister	minister	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
then	then	RB	B-ADVP	O
take	take	VB	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
recess	recess	NN	I-NP	O
until	until	IN	B-PP	O
one	one	CD	B-NP	O
month	month	NN	I-NP	O
before	before	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
deadline	deadline	NN	I-NP	O
imgflip.com	imgflip.com	NN	I-NP	O
				
kwai	kwai	FW	B-NP	O
gkwa	gkwa	FW	I-NP	O
0964	0964	CD	I-NP	O
#	#	#	I-NP	O
nnevvy	nnevvy	JJ	I-NP	O
applause	applause	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
Thais	Thais	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
Hong	Hong	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Kong	Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
WHY	WHY	NNP	I-NP	O
THAIS	THAIS	NNP	I-NP	O
DID	DID	NNP	I-NP	O
NOT	NOT	NNP	I-NP	O
GET	GET	NNP	I-NP	O
HURT	HURT	NNP	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
CULTURAL	CULTURAL	NNP	B-NP	O
DIFFERENCE	DIFFERENCE	NNP	I-NP	O
JUST	JUST	NNP	I-NP	O
STAY	STAY	NNP	I-NP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
WALL	WALL	NN	I-NP	O
				
So	so	RB	B-ADVP	O
,	,	,	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
order	order	VBP	B-VP	O
this	this	DT	B-NP	O
foce	foce	NN	I-NP	O
mask	mask	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
protect	protect	VB	I-VP	O
ogainst	ogainst	JJ	B-NP	O
fhe	fhe	NN	I-NP	O
Corond	Corond	NNP	I-NP	O
virus	virus	NNP	I-NP	O
Hooold	Hooold	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
up	up	IN	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
says	say	VBZ	B-VP	O
something	something	NN	B-NP	O
here	here	RB	B-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Made	make	VBN	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
				
best	good	JJS	B-NP	O
candidate	candidate	NN	I-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
JA	JA	NNP	B-NP	O
2020	2020	CD	I-NP	O
joe	joe	NN	I-NP	O
biden	biden	NN	I-NP	O
Kamala	Kamala	NNP	I-NP	O
harris	harris	NNP	I-NP	O
Bernie	Bernie	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
sanders	sander	NNS	I-NP	O
TikTok	TikTok	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
@	@	SYM	O	O
eliguthrie	eliguthrie	NN	B-NP	O
				
BREAKING	BREAK	VBG	B-VP	B-ORG
NEWS	NEWS	NN	B-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
EL	EL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
CH	CH	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
AND	AND	CC	O	I-ORG
MANNEQUINS	MANNEQUINS	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
THEN	THEN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HE	HE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BOUGHT	BOUGHT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LINGERIE	LINGERIE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
FOR	FOR	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
NEWS	NEWS	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
AWOMAN	AWOMAN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WHO	WHO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WAS	WAS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SEEN	SEEN	NNP	I-NP	O
OUTSIDE	OUTSIDE	NNP	I-NP	O
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	O
STORE	STORE	NNP	I-NP	O
WEARING	WEARING	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
MAN	MAN	NNP	I-NP	O
WEARING	WEARING	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
DONALD	DONALD	NNP	I-NP	O
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	O
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	O
WENT	WENT	NNP	I-NP	O
INTO	INTO	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
VICTORIA	VICTORIA	NNP	I-NP	O
SECRET	SECRET	NNP	I-NP	O
STORE	STORE	NNP	I-NP	O
OLGED	OLGED	NNP	I-NP	O
FEMALE	FEMALE	NNP	I-NP	O
CUSTOMERS	CUSTOMERS	NNP	I-NP	O
HAN	HAN	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
MEIANIA	MEIANIA	NNP	I-NP	O
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	O
MASKWHO	MASKWHO	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
WASWAITING	WASWAITING	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
FOR	FOR	IN	O	O
HIM	HIM	PRP	O	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
COME	COME	NNP	B-NP	O
OUT	OUT	NNP	I-NP	O
SAM	SAM	NNP	I-NP	O
WE	WE	PRP	O	O
HAVE	HAVE	VBP	B-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
SURVEILLANCE	SURVEILLANCE	NN	I-NP	O
imgfip.com	imgfip.com	JJ	I-NP	O
FILM	FILM	NN	I-NP	O
AT	AT	IN	B-PP	O
11	11	CD	B-NP	O
Ron	Ron	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Burgundy	Burgundy	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Meme	Meme	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
-	-	:	O	O
Imgflip	Imgflip	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
ANNEL	ANNEL	NNP	I-NP	O
S	S	NNP	I-NP	O
TEAM	TEAM	NNP	I-NP	O
				
MASK	MASK	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
DEN	DEN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CE	CE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Help	Help	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
child	child	NN	I-NP	O
find	find	VB	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
right	right	JJ	I-NP	O
Halloween	Halloween	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
costume	costume	NN	I-NP	O
				
#	#	#	B-NP	O
Hantavirus	Hantavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
China	China	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
discovered	discover	VBD	B-VP	O
new	new	JJ	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
Whole	whole	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
right	right	RB	B-ADVP	O
now	now	RB	I-ADVP	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
finally	finally	RB	B-NP	O
2020	2020	CD	I-NP	O
but	but	CC	O	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
realize	realize	VBP	B-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
both	both	DT	B-NP	O
1820	1820	CD	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
1920	1920	CD	B-NP	O
had	have	VBD	B-VP	O
massive	massive	JJ	B-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
outbreaks	outbreak	NNS	I-NP	O
In	in	IN	B-PP	O
regards	regards	NNS	B-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
recent	recent	JJ	I-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
spreading	spread	VBG	B-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
.	.	.	O	O
				
nese	nese	DT	B-NP	O
NewYear	NewYear	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Chira	Chira	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
attermpt	attermpt	NN	I-NP	O
at	at	IN	B-VP	O
controlling	control	VBG	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
pandemi	pandemi	NN	I-NP	O
Wuhan	Wuhan	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
Hantavirus	Hantavirus	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Man	man	NN	B-NP	O
dies	die	VBZ	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
ca	can	MD	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
get	get	VB	B-VP	O
any	any	DT	B-NP	O
worse	bad	JJR	I-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
after	after	IN	B-VP	O
testing	test	VBG	I-VP	O
positive	positive	JJ	B-AP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
new	new	JJ	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Hantavirus	Hantavirus	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
We	we	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
doing	do	VBG	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
sequel	sequel	NN	I-NP	O
				
Dr	Dr	NNP	B-NP	O
Grayfang	Grayfang	NNP	I-NP	O
@	@	NNP	I-NP	O
OrGrayfang	OrGrayfang	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
ha	ha	FW	I-NP	O
tete	tete	FW	I-NP	O
dryteng	dryteng	FW	I-NP	O
ang	ang	FW	I-NP	O
yay	yay	FW	I-NP	O
a	a	DT	O	O
Me	me	PRP	O	O
getting	get	VBG	B-VP	O
food	food	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
alcohol	alcohol	NN	B-NP	O
delivered	deliver	VBN	B-VP	O
during	during	IN	O	O
quarantine	quarantine	FW	O	O
enhhan	enhhan	FW	O	O
g	g	FW	O	O
do	do	FW	O	O
bt	bt	FW	O	O
oa	oa	FW	O	O
rear	rear	FW	O	O
a	a	FW	O	O
Ve	ve	FW	O	O
ha	ha	FW	O	O
ne	ne	FW	O	O
he	he	FW	O	O
oe	oe	FW	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
fe	fe	NN	B-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
TEN	TEN	NNP	B-NP	O
D	D	NNP	I-NP	O
laper	laper	NN	I-NP	O
Leave	leave	VB	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
doornte	doornte	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
get	get	VB	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
bell	bell	NN	I-NP	O
out	out	IN	O	O
of	of	IN	O	O
here	here	RB	B-ADVP	O
				
Henh	henh	RB	B-ADVP	O
After	after	IN	B-PP	O
corona	corona	JJ	B-NP	O
swine	swine	NN	I-NP	O
flu	flu	NN	I-NP	O
bubonicplague	bubonicplague	NN	I-NP	O
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
been	be	VBN	I-VP	O
detected	detect	VBN	I-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
china	china	NN	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
We	we	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
endgame	endgame	NN	I-NP	O
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	B-NP	O
BUILT	BUILT	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
WALL	WALL	NNP	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
AND	AND	CC	O	O
THEY	THEY	PRP	O	O
HAVE	HAVE	VBP	B-VP	O
ALMOST	ALMOST	NNP	B-NP	O
NO	NO	NNP	I-NP	O
MEXICANS	MEXICANS	NNPS	I-NP	O
CASE	CASE	NN	I-NP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
POINT	POINT	NN	B-NP	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
s	s	PRP	B-NP	O
finally	finally	RB	I-NP	O
2020	2020	CD	I-NP	O
but	but	CC	O	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
reakze	reakze	VBP	B-VP	O
that	that	DT	B-NP	O
boch	boch	NN	I-NP	O
1820	1820	CD	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
1920	1920	CD	B-NP	O
had	have	VBD	B-VP	O
massive	massive	JJ	B-NP	O
vew	vew	JJ	I-NP	O
v	v	NN	I-NP	O
s	s	VBZ	B-VP	O
S	S	NNP	B-NP	O
May	may	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
ted	t	VBN	I-VP	O
Myte	Myte	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
ein	ein	FW	I-NP	O
tha	tha	FW	I-NP	O
plague	plague	FW	I-NP	O
outbreoks	outbreoks	FW	I-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
begun	begin	VBN	I-VP	O
killing	kill	VBG	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Karens	Karens	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
PLAY	PLAY	NNP	B-NP	O
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
SAFE	SAFE	NNP	I-NP	O
DO	DO	NNP	I-NP	O
N'T	N'T	NNP	I-NP	O
WORRY	WORRY	NNP	I-NP	O
LEAVE	LEAVE	NNP	I-NP	O
OUR	OUR	NNP	I-NP	O
BORDERS	BORDERS	NNP	I-NP	O
ОРEN	ОРEN	NNP	I-NP	O
SHUT	SHUT	NNP	I-NP	O
OUR	OUR	NNP	I-NP	O
BORDERS	BORDERS	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	NNP	I-NP	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	O
NOW	NOW	RB	B-NP	O
98	98	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
LEAVE	LEAVE	NNP	I-NP	O
THEM	THEM	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
OPEN	OPEN	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
CLOSE	CLOSE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
THEM	THEM	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
NOW	NOW	RB	B-ADVP	I-MISC
This	this	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
pal	pal	NN	I-NP	O
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
ended	end	VBN	I-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
33.K	33.K	CD	B-NP	O
Vates	vate	NNS	I-NP	O
				
Reporter	reporter	NN	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
why	why	WRB	B-ADVP	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
calling	call	VBG	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
Trump	trump	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
because	because	IN	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
came	come	VBD	B-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Reporter	Reporter	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
think	think	VB	B-VP	O
thats	that	NNS	B-NP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
little	little	JJ	I-NP	O
racist	racist	NN	I-NP	O
tho	tho	IN	B-PP	O
Trump	Trump	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
Oit	Oit	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
came	come	VBD	B-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
CHI-NA	CHI-NA	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
				
Actual	actual	JJ	B-NP	O
footage	footage	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
Jared	Jared	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Leto	Leto	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
returning	return	VBG	B-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
his	his	PRP$	B-NP	O
12	12	CD	I-NP	O
day	day	NN	I-NP	O
meditation	meditation	NN	I-NP	O
retreat	retreat	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
learning	learn	VBG	B-VP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
coronavirus	coronavirus	JJ	B-NP	O
adan	adan	NN	I-NP	O
tore	tear	VBD	B-VP	O
Ca	Ca	NNP	B-NP	O
The	The	NNP	I-NP	O
p	p	NNP	I-NP	O
Lhed	Lhed	NNP	I-NP	O
etend	etend	FW	I-NP	O
en	en	FW	I-NP	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
student	student	NN	I-NP	O
starts	start	VBZ	B-VP	O
coughing	cough	VBG	I-VP	O
time	time	NN	B-NP	O
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
come	come	VBN	I-VP	O
hmm	hmm	NN	B-NP	O
				
Internet	Internet	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Explorer	Explorer	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
@	@	IN	B-PP	O
internetexp	internetexp	NN	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Breaking	Breaking	NNP	B-NP	O
News	News	NNP	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
2	2	CD	B-NP	O
reported	report	VBD	B-VP	O
cases	case	NNS	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
03:11	03:11	CD	I-NP	O
PM	PM	NNP	I-NP	O
-	-	:	O	O
18	18	CD	B-NP	O
Mar	Mar	NNP	I-NP	O
20	20	CD	I-NP	O
42	42	CD	I-NP	O
Likes	like	NNS	I-NP	O
				
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
exist	exist	VB	B-VP	O
Everyone	everyone	NN	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
oh	oh	UH	O	O
its	its	PRP$	O	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
china	china	NN	B-NP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
too	too	RB	B-ADVP	O
far	far	RB	I-ADVP	O
away	away	RB	I-ADVP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
get	get	VB	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	O	O
me	me	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Coranavirus	Coranavirus	NNP	B-NP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
month	month	NN	I-NP	O
later	later	RB	B-ADVP	O
:	:	:	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
like	like	VBP	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
move	move	VB	I-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
move	move	VB	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
				
Coronavirus-safe	coronavirus-safe	JJ	B-AP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
Isolation	Isolation	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Face	Face	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
mask	mask	NN	I-NP	O
Gloves	glove	NNS	I-NP	O
				
They	they	PRP	O	O
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
had	have	VBN	I-VP	O
US	US	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
cowering	cower	VBG	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	O	O
over	over	IN	B-PP	O
half	half	PDT	B-NP	O
a	a	DT	I-NP	O
century	century	NN	I-NP	O
Ore	Ore	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
3	3	CD	B-NP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
4	4	CD	B-NP	O
century	century	NN	I-NP	O
Good	good	JJ	I-NP	O
lil	lil	NN	I-NP	O
Sheeple	Sheeple	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
ng	ng	IN	B-PP	O
flip.com	flip.com	NN	B-NP	O
				
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Kung	Kung	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Flu	Flu	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
				
Government	government	NN	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Stay	stay	VB	B-VP	O
inside	inside	IN	B-PP	O
Half	Half	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
US	US	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
population	population	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Catch	catch	VB	B-VP	O
me	me	PRP	O	O
outside	outside	IN	O	O
how	how	WRB	B-ADVP	O
bow	bow	JJ	B-NP	O
dat	dat	NN	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
Phil	Phil	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
STARECAT.COM	STARECAT.COM	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
Congratulatios	congratulatio	NNS	B-NP	O
You	you	PRP	O	O
Have	have	VBP	B-VP	B-ORG
Won	Won	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
martk	martk	NN	I-NP	O
Free	Free	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Trip	Trip	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
To	To	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
China	China	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
Chelsea	Chelsea	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Clinton	Clinton	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
@	@	IN	B-PP	O
ChelseaClinton	ChelseaClinton	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
President	President	NNP	I-NP	O
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
left	leave	VBN	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
U.S.	U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
dangerously	dangerously	RB	B-ADVP	O
underprepared	underprepare	VBN	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
face	face	VB	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
public	public	JJ	I-NP	O
health	health	NN	I-NP	O
crisis	crisis	NN	I-NP	O
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
#	#	#	I-NP	O
coronavirus	coronavirus	JJ	I-NP	O
outbreak.	outbreak.	NN	I-NP	O
@	@	SYM	O	O
devisridhar	devisridhar	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
explain	explain	VBP	B-VP	O
how	how	WRB	B-ADVP	O
via	via	IN	B-PP	O
@	@	NNP	B-NP	O
CNN	CNN	NNP	I-NP	O
Lars	Lars	NNP	I-NP	O
Printzén	Printzén	NNP	I-NP	O
@	@	NNP	I-NP	O
LarsPrintzen	LarsPrintzen	NNP	I-NP	O
Feb	Feb	NNP	I-NP	O
25	25	CD	I-NP	O
Replying	reply	VBG	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
pChelseaClinton	pChelseaClinton	NNP	B-NP	O
@	@	IN	B-PP	O
devisridhar	devisridhar	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
@	@	IN	B-PP	O
CNN	CNN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
So	so	RB	B-NP	O
far	far	RB	I-NP	O
more	more	JJR	I-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
US	US	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
died	die	VBN	I-VP	O
trying	try	VBG	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
testify	testify	VB	I-VP	O
against	against	IN	B-PP	O
you	you	PRP	B-NP	O
mother	mother	NN	I-NP	O
than	than	IN	O	O
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
died	die	VBN	I-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
.	.	.	O	O
				
COVID	COVID	NN	B-NP	O
FACTS	FACTS	NNS	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Per	per	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
CDC	CDC	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
elfective	elfective	JJ	I-NP	O
07	07	CD	I-NP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
10	10	CD	B-NP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
US	US	NNP	I-NP	O
POPULATION	POPULATION	NNP	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
329,934,000	329,934,000	CD	B-NP	O
Covid	Covid	NNP	I-NP	O
Cases	Case	NNPS	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
3,106,931	3,106,931	CD	B-NP	O
Deaths	Death	NNPS	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
132,855	132,855	CD	B-NP	O
That	that	DT	B-VP	O
means	mean	VBZ	I-VP	O
only	only	RB	B-NP	O
0.4	0.4	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
(	(	(	O	O
less	less	JJR	B-AP	O
than	than	IN	B-PP	O
1	1	CD	B-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
)	)	)	O	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
Americans	American	NNPS	B-NP	B-MISC
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
even	even	RB	B-ADVP	O
contracted	contract	VBN	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
It	it	PRP	O	O
also	also	RB	B-ADVP	O
means	mean	VBZ	B-VP	O
95.72	95.72	CD	B-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	O	O
those	those	DT	B-AP	O
survive	survive	JJ	I-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Best	good	JJS	B-AP	O
of	of	IN	O	O
all	all	DT	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
only	only	RB	B-NP	O
0.04	0.04	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
Americans	American	NNPS	B-NP	B-MISC
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
dled	dle	VBN	I-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
this	this	DT	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
99.96	99.96	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
survival	survival	NN	I-NP	O
rate	rate	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
You	you	PRP	O	O
dan'l	dan'l	MD	B-VP	O
see	see	VB	I-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
hese	hese	JJ	B-NP	O
masks	mask	NNS	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
reulriclions	reulriclion	NNS	B-NP	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
polically	polically	RB	I-ADVP	O
motivated	motivate	VBN	B-VP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
A'Ruse	A'Ruse	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
Defined	define	VBN	B-VP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
113.000	113.000	CD	B-NP	O
PEOPLE	PEOPLE	NNS	I-NP	O
HAVE	HAVE	VBP	B-VP	O
RECOVERED	RECOVER	VBN	I-VP	O
FROM	FROM	IN	B-PP	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
TRY	TRY	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
SHARING	SHARING	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
THAT	THAT	WDT	B-NP	I-MISC
INSTEAD	INSTEAD	RB	B-ADVP	I-MISC
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	I-MISC
cases	case	NNS	B-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
NOT	NOT	RB	B-NP	O
recoveries	recovery	NNS	I-NP	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
DEFINED	DEFIN	VBN	I-VP	O
				
Does	do	VBZ	B-VP	O
that	that	DT	B-NP	O
coviD	coviD	JJ	I-NP	O
bill	bill	NN	I-NP	O
include	include	VBP	B-VP	O
10	10	CD	B-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
BIG	BIG	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
GUY	GUY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
?	?	.	O	O
				
FICTION	FICTION	NN	B-NP	O
NEEDS	NEED	VBZ	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
BE	BE	VB	I-VP	O
SOMEWHAT	SOMEWHAT	RB	B-AP	O
REALISTIC	REALISTIC	JJ	I-AP	O
FOR	FOR	IN	B-PP	O
PEOPLE	PEOPLE	NNS	B-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
BELIEVE	BELIEVE	VB	I-VP	O
IT	IT	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
REALITY	REALITY	NN	B-NP	O
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	O
UNDER	UNDER	IN	B-PP	O
NO	NO	DT	B-NP	O
SUCH	SUCH	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
CONSTRAINT	CONSTRAINT	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
REAL	REAL	JJ	B-NP	O
WORKER	WORKER	NN	I-NP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
MARCH	MARCH	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
2020	2020	CD	I-NP	O
				
Mecessit	mecessit	NN	B-NP	B-PER
Is	be	VBZ	B-VP	I-PER
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
mother	mother	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
oll	oll	NN	B-NP	O
inventions	invention	NNS	I-NP	O
THEFUNNYBEAVER.COM	THEFUNNYBEAVER.COM	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
@	@	SYM	O	O
all-in	all-in	FW	O	O
un	un	FW	O	O
ana	ana	FW	O	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
m	m	NN	I-NP	O
DITRY	DITRY	NN	I-NP	O
口	口	NN	I-NP	O
BEFORE	BEFORE	IN	B-PP	O
AFTER	AFTER	NNP	B-NP	O
OUR	OUR	NNP	I-NP	O
NORWEGIAN	NORWEGIAN	NNP	I-NP	O
POKER	POKER	NNP	I-NP	O
TRANSLATOR	TRANSLATOR	NNP	I-NP	O
IN	IN	NNP	I-NP	O
LOCKDOWN	LOCKDOWN	NNP	I-NP	O
				
BARACK	BARACK	NNP	B-NP	O
OBAMA	OBAMA	NNP	I-NP	O
PRESENTS	PRESENTS	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
MEDAL	MEDAL	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	O	O
HIMSELF	HIMSELF	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
FOR	FOR	IN	B-VP	O
CREATING	CREAT	VBG	I-VP	O
JOBS	JOBS	NNS	B-NP	O
DURING	DURING	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	B-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
ADMINISTRATION	ADMINISTRATION	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
				
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
types	type	NNS	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
communists	communist	NNS	B-NP	O
				
Officials	Officials	NNP	B-NP	O
Just	Just	NNP	I-NP	O
Confirmed	Confirmed	NNP	I-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
Mystery	Mystery	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Spreads	Spread	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG
by	by	IN	B-PP	O
Human	Human	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
Human	Human	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Transmission	Transmission	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
guy	guy	NN	I-NP	O
Playing	Playing	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Plague	Plague	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Inc.	Inc.	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Area	area	NN	I-NP	B-MISC
51	51	CD	I-NP	O
Computer	computer	NN	I-NP	O
				
*	*	SYM	O	O
New	New	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Swine	Swine	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
flu	flu	NN	I-NP	O
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
virus	virus	NN	B-NP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
human	human	JJ	B-NP	O
pandemic	pandemic	JJ	I-NP	O
potential	potential	NN	I-NP	O
found	find	VBN	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
*	*	SYM	O	O
Whole	whole	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
AAE	AAE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
BAND	BAND	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
KAR	KAR	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
BAND	BAND	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
KARI	KARI	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
Hob	Hob	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
He	he	PRP	O	O
voted	vote	VBD	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
Trump	Trump	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
.	.	.	O	O
				
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
Bob	Bob	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
friend	friend	NN	I-NP	O
Sally	Sally	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
.	.	.	O	O
				
Sally	sally	RB	B-ADVP	O
voted	vote	VBD	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
Clinton	Clinton	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
.	.	.	O	O
				
Botre	Botre	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Satlyare	Satlyare	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
stilt	still	VBD	B-VP	O
frienda-beenese-Bob-and-Sallyare-both-adulte	frienda-beenese-Bob-and-Sallyare-both-adulte	JJ	B-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Bettke	Bettke	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Botramt	Botramt	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Sally	Sally	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
.	.	.	O	O
				
1720	1720	CD	B-NP	O
1820	1820	CD	I-NP	O
1920	1920	CD	I-NP	O
2020	2020	CD	I-NP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Bubonic	Bubonic	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Plague	Plague	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Plagu	Plagu	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Chelera	Chelera	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Outbreak	Outbreak	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Coincidence	Coincidence	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
I	I	PRP	O	O
THINK	THINK	VBP	B-VP	B-ORG
NOT	NOT	RB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
				
What	what	WP	B-NP	O
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
Donald	Donald	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
and	and	CC	O	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Pumpkin	Pumpkin	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
Common	Common	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
?	?	.	O	O
				
They	they	PRP	O	O
re	re	VBP	B-VP	O
Orange	Orange	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
outside	outside	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
Hollow	Hollow	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Inside	Inside	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
and	and	CC	O	O
should	shall	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
tossed	toss	VBN	I-VP	O
out	out	RP	I-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
early	early	JJ	B-NP	O
November	November	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Chance	chance	NN	B-NP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
99.97	99.97	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
recovery	recovery	NN	I-NP	O
rate	rate	NN	I-NP	O
•	•	SYM	O	O
FALSE	FALSE	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Alter	Alter	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
DNA	DNA	NN	I-NP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
an	an	DT	B-NP	O
experimental	experimental	JJ	I-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
NO	NO	DT	B-NP	O
liabilty	liabilty	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
corrupt	corrupt	JJ	I-NP	O
industry	industry	NN	I-NP	O
				
re	re	VB	B-VP	O
Photos	Photos	NNP	B-NP	O
IF	IF	NNP	I-NP	O
YOU	YOU	NNP	I-NP	O
LOVE	LOVE	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
AMERICA	AMERICA	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
,	,	,	O	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
'RE	'RE	VBP	B-VP	O
GENERALLY	GENERALLY	NNP	B-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
CONSERVATIVE	CONSERVATIVE	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
IF	IF	IN	O	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
HATE	HATE	VBP	B-VP	B-MISC
AMERICA	AMERICA	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	I-MISC
'RE	'RE	VBP	B-VP	I-MISC
USUALLY	USUALLY	RB	B-ADVP	I-MISC
A	A	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
LIBERAL	LIBERAL	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Cprione	Cprione	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
				
Pfizer	Pfizer	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Peeple	Peeple	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
working	work	VBG	B-VP	O
at	at	IN	B-PP	O
home	home	NN	B-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
Sweatpants	sweatpants	NNS	B-NP	B-LOC
				
having	have	VBG	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
bad	bad	JJ	I-NP	O
day	day	NN	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
remember	remember	VB	B-VP	O
that	that	DT	B-NP	O
time	time	NN	I-NP	O
obama	obama	NN	I-NP	O
lost	lose	VBD	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
when	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
he	he	PRP	O	O
saw	see	VBD	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
baby	baby	NN	I-NP	O
dressed	dress	VBN	B-VP	O
as	as	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
pope	pope	NN	I-NP	O
				
JUST	JUST	RB	B-ADVP	O
HAD	HAD	VBD	B-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
VACCINE	VACCINE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
FEELING	FEELING	NNP	I-NP	O
GREAT	GREAT	NNP	I-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
makeameme.org	makeameme.org	NN	B-NP	O
				
Whole	whole	JJ	B-NP	O
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
Thinking	think	VBG	B-VP	O
corona	corona	JJ	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
will	will	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
end	end	VB	I-VP	O
soon	soon	RB	B-ADVP	O
*	*	SYM	O	O
Hantavirus	Hantavirus	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
				
ES	ES	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
CW	CW	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Newe	Newe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ME	ME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
RCE	RCE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Corporate	Corporate	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
needs	need	VBZ	B-VP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
find	find	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
differences	difference	NNS	I-NP	O
between	between	IN	B-PP	O
this	this	DT	B-NP	O
picture	picture	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
this	this	DT	B-NP	O
picture	picture	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
They	they	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
same	same	JJ	I-NP	O
picture	picture	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Me	me	PRP	O	O
when	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
get	get	VBP	B-VP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
covid	covid	JJ	I-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
MemeZila.com	MemeZila.com	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
HECHEVS	HECHEVS	NNS	B-NP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
WHITE	WHITE	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
HC	HC	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WASHINGTON	WASHINGTON	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NIK	NIK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NEWS	NEWS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SPECIAL	SPECIAL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
REPORT	REPORT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LIVE	LIVE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WHITE	WHITE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HOUSE	HOUSE	NNP	I-NP	O
BRIEFING	BRIEFING	NNP	I-NP	O
FROM	FROM	NNP	I-NP	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	O
TASK	TASK	NNP	I-NP	O
FORCE	FORCE	NNP	I-NP	O
FOR	FOR	IN	B-PP	O
LATEST	LATEST	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
UPDATES	UPDATES	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
GO	GO	VB	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
NBCNEWS.COM	NBCNEWS.COM	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
/	/	SYM	O	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	B-NP	O
				
society	society	NN	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
#	#	#	B-NP	O
stayhome	stayhome	JJ	I-NP	O
homeless	homeless	JJ	I-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
				
Just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
case	case	NN	B-NP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
wondering	wonder	VBG	I-VP	O
how	how	WRB	B-ADVP	O
much	much	JJ	B-AP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
media	media	NNS	I-NP	O
controls	control	VBZ	I-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
America	America	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
been	be	VBN	I-VP	O
vaccinating	vaccinate	VBG	I-VP	O
cattle	cattle	NNS	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
coronavirus	coronavirus	NN	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
years	year	NNS	B-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
yet	yet	CC	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
news	news	NN	I-NP	O
tells	tell	VBZ	B-VP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
new	new	JJ	B-AP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
gunna	gunna	NN	B-NP	O
kill	kill	VB	B-VP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
all	all	DT	B-ADVP	O
so	so	RB	I-ADVP	O
go	go	VB	B-VP	O
buy	buy	JJ	B-NP	O
mask	mask	NN	I-NP	O
..	..	.	O	O
10	10	CD	B-NP	O
doses	dose	NNS	I-NP	O
20	20	CD	I-NP	O
ml	ml	NN	I-NP	O
Bovine	Bovine	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Rotavirus	Rotavirus	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
-	-	:	O	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Vaccine	Vaccine	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Klled	Klled	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Escherichia	Escherichia	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Coli	Coli	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Bacterin	Bacterin	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
For	for	IN	B-PP	O
veterinary	veterinary	JJ	B-NP	O
use	use	NN	I-NP	O
only	only	RB	B-ADVP	O
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
can	can	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
contracted	contract	VBN	I-VP	O
only	only	RB	B-ADVP	O
through	through	IN	B-PP	O
human	human	JJ	B-NP	O
contact	contact	NN	I-NP	O
Introverts	introvert	NNS	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
				
17h	17h	CD	B-NP	O
-	-	:	O	O
0	0	CD	B-NP	O
Lighten	Lighten	NNP	I-NP	O
up	up	RP	I-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
WHY	WHY	WRB	B-ADVP	O
BIDEN	BIDEN	NNP	B-NP	O
NO	NO	NNP	I-NP	O
GET	GET	NNP	I-NP	O
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
In	in	IN	B-PP	O
casee	casee	NN	B-NP	O
mnks	mnk	NNS	I-NP	O
e	e	VBP	B-VP	O
otola	otola	NN	B-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
finally	finally	RB	B-NP	O
2020	2020	CD	I-NP	O
but	but	CC	O	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
realize	realize	VBP	B-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
both	both	DT	B-NP	O
1820	1820	CD	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
1920	1920	CD	B-NP	O
had	have	VBD	B-VP	O
massive	massive	JJ	B-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
outbreaks	outbreak	NNS	I-NP	O
Hmm	Hmm	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
ban	ban	VB	I-VP	O
online	online	JJ	B-NP	O
gaming	gaming	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
chatting	chat	VBG	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
foreigners	foreigner	NNS	B-NP	O
outside	outside	IN	B-PP	O
Great	Great	NNP	B-NP	O
Firewall	Firewall	NNP	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
report	report	NN	B-NP	O
cor	cor	NN	I-NP	O
psychopathic	psychopathic	JJ	I-NP	O
idisc	idisc	NN	I-NP	O
You	you	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
never	never	RB	B-ADVP	O
going	go	VBG	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
see	see	VB	I-VP	O
those	those	DT	B-NP	O
freaky	freaky	JJ	I-NP	O
friends	friend	NNS	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
yours	your	NNS	B-NP	O
again	again	RB	B-ADVP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
Never	never	RB	B-ADVP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	B-NP	O
TESTING	TESTING	NNP	I-NP	O
SC	SC	NNP	I-NP	O
M	M	NNP	I-NP	O
TH	TH	NNP	I-NP	O
LARS	LARS	NNP	I-NP	O
Interesting	Interesting	NNP	I-NP	O
how	how	WRB	B-ADVP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
US	US	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
government	government	NN	I-NP	O
labels	label	VBZ	B-VP	O
corona	corona	JJ	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
patients	patient	NNS	I-NP	O
Consumers	consumer	NNS	I-NP	O
				
stop	stop	VB	B-VP	O
calling	call	VBG	I-VP	O
it	it	PRP	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
china	china	NN	I-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
spanish	spanish	JJ	I-NP	O
flu	flu	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
				
Funny	Funny	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
how	how	WRB	B-ADVP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
popped	pop	VBD	B-VP	O
up	up	RP	I-VP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
suddenly	suddenly	RB	B-ADVP	O
theres	there	VBZ	B-VP	O
no	no	DT	B-NP	O
more	more	JJR	I-NP	O
Hong	Hong	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Kóng	Kóng	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
protestors	protestor	NNS	I-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
China	China	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
				
me	me	PRP	O	O
serving	serve	VBG	B-VP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
kids	kid	NNS	I-NP	O
quarantine	quarantine	JJ	I-NP	O
pizza	pizza	NN	I-NP	O
made	make	VBN	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
tortillas	tortilla	NNS	B-NP	O
eifeandtimesofmom	eifeandtimesofmom	FW	I-NP	O
Buongiorno	Buongiorno	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
CAT	CAT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
MEME	MEME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
GOES	GOES	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
UIRAL	UIRAL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IΝ	IΝ	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OUTBREAK	OUTBREAK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
PANDEMIC	PANDEMIC	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SeethChina	SeethChina	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Mrni	Mrni	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
t	t	NN	I-NP	O
				
IF	IF	IN	B-PP	O
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
CAME	CAME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
FROM	FROM	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
WUHAN	WUHAN	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
THEN	THEN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HOW	HOW	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	O
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	O
RACIST	RACIST	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
CALL	CALL	VB	B-VP	O
ITTHE	ITTHE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WUHAN	WUHAN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CORONA	CORONA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
?	?	.	O	O
				
Steve	Steve	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
King	King	NNP	I-NP	O
999	999	CD	I-NP	O
ACCORDING	ACCORD	VBG	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
CNN	CNN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
TOOK	TOOK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OBAMA	OBAMA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
MLLIONS	MLLIONS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
INFECTED	INFECTED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
AND	AND	CC	O	O
OVER	OVER	IN	B-PP	O
1,000	1,000	CD	B-NP	O
DEATHS	DEATHS	NNS	I-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
DECLARE	DECLARE	VB	I-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
HINI	HINI	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
FLU	FLU	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
HEALTH	HEALTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EMERGENCY	EMERGENCY	NNP	I-NP	O
POINTOSA	POINTOSA	NNP	I-NP	O
UNDER	UNDER	NNP	I-NP	O
PRESIDENTTRUMP	PRESIDENTTRUMP	NNP	I-NP	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	O
WAS	WAS	NNP	I-NP	O
DECLARED	DECLARED	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
HEALTH	HEALTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EMERGENCY	EMERGENCY	NNP	I-NP	O
AND	AND	CC	O	O
PUBLIC	PUBLIC	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
SAFETY	SAFETY	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
MEASURES	MEASURES	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
WERE	WERE	VBD	B-VP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
PLACE	PLACE	NNP	B-NP	O
BEFORE	BEFORE	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
SINGLE	SINGLE	NNP	I-NP	O
U.S.	U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
DEATH	DEATH	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
O0CCURRED	O0CCURRED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
260	260	CD	I-NP	O
Cermeres	Cermeres	NNP	I-NP	O
K	K	NNP	I-NP	O
Shares	Share	NNPS	I-NP	O
				
when	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
've	have	VBP	B-VP	O
been	be	VBN	I-VP	O
hiding	hide	VBG	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
zombie	zombie	NN	I-NP	O
bite	bite	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
can	can	MD	B-VP	O
feel	feel	VB	I-VP	O
yourself	yourself	PRP	O	O
starting	start	VBG	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
turn	turn	VB	I-VP	O
but	but	CC	O	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
want	want	VB	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
tell	tell	VB	I-VP	O
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
group	group	NN	I-NP	O
de	de	FW	I-NP	O
wfauft	wfauft	FW	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
ALSO	ALSO	RB	B-NP	O
DUDE	DUDE	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	I-ORG
NOT	NOT	RB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
PREFERRED	PREFERRED	JJ	I-NP	I-ORG
NOMENCLATURE	NOMENCLATURE	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
COVID19	COVID19	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
PLEASE	PLEASE	VB	B-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Obama	Obama	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Whispers	whisper	NNS	B-NP	O
put	put	VBD	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
laser	laser	NN	I-NP	O
pointer	pointer	NN	I-NP	O
away	away	RB	B-ADVP	O
or	or	CC	O	O
give	give	VB	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
to	to	TO	O	O
me	me	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
ML	ML	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
DOCD	DOCD	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
spreading	spread	VBG	B-VP	O
through	through	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Hong	Hong	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
Kong	Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
gets	get	VBZ	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
longer	long	JJR	I-NP	O
holiday	holiday	NN	I-NP	O
				
James	James	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Woods	Woods	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
e	e	NNP	I-NP	O
@	@	NNP	I-NP	O
RealJames	RealJames	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
.	.	.	O	O
				
13	13	CD	B-NP	O
Aug	Aug	NNP	I-NP	O
v	v	NN	I-NP	O
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
our	our	PRP$	B-NP	O
last	last	JJ	I-NP	O
stand	stand	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
folks	folk	NNS	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
And	and	CC	O	O
here	here	RB	B-ADVP	O
's	's	POS	I-ADVP	O
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
last	last	JJ	I-NP	O
defender	defender	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
If	if	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
take	take	VBP	B-VP	O
him	him	PRP	O	O
down	down	RP	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
America	America	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
gone	go	VBN	I-VP	O
forever	forever	RB	B-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Vote	vote	NN	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
@	@	NNP	B-NP	O
realDonald	realDonald	NNP	I-NP	O
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
life	life	NN	I-NP	O
depends	depend	VBZ	B-VP	O
on	on	IN	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
24K	24K	JJ	B-NP	O
13	13	CD	I-NP	O
76.2K	76.2K	NNP	I-NP	O
174K	174K	NNP	I-NP	O
				
MY	MY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
GOVERNMENT	GOVERNMENT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WILL	WILL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
KEEP	KEEP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ME	ME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SAFE	SAFE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
FROM	FROM	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
AN	AN	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
INVISIBLE	INVISIBLE	JJ	I-NP	I-ORG
ENEMY	ENEMY	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
BASED	BAS	VBN	B-VP	O
ON	ON	IN	B-PP	O
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
FLAWED	FLAWED	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
MATHEMATICAL	MATHEMATICAL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
MODEL	MODEL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BY	BY	IN	B-VP	I-ORG
PUTTING	PUTT	VBG	I-VP	I-ORG
ME	ME	PRP	O	I-ORG
UNDER	UNDER	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
HOUSE	HOUSE	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
ARREST	ARREST	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
MAKING	MAKING	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
ME	ME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
UNEMPLOYED	UNEMPLOYED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
RATTING	RATTING	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OUT	OUT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
MY	MY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NEIGHBOURS	NEIGHBOURS	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG
AND	AND	CC	O	I-ORG
TAKING	TAKING	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
AWAY	AWAY	NNP	I-NP	O
MY	MY	NNP	I-NP	O
HUMAN	HUMAN	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
RIGHTS	RIGHTS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
ACCORDING	ACCORD	VBG	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
CNN	CNN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
ITOCY	ITOCY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
B.M	B.M	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
MLLIONS	MLLIONS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
INFECTED	INFECTED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
AND	AND	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VE	VE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
OU	OU	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
LEATHS	LEATHS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
DECLARE	DECLARE	VB	I-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
H1	H1	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
11	11	CD	B-NP	O
FLU	FLU	NNP	I-NP	O
AEAZTH	AEAZTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EMERGENCY	EMERGENCY	NNP	I-NP	O
NG	NG	NNP	I-NP	O
TURNIN	TURNIN	NNP	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
PÕII	PÕII	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
TU	TU	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
UNDER	UNDER	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
PRESIDENT	PRESIDENT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WAS	WAS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
DECLARED	DECLARED	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
HEALTH	HEALTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EMERGENCY	EMERGENCY	NNP	I-NP	O
AND	AND	CC	O	O
PUBLIC	PUBLIC	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
SAFETY	SAFETY	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
MEASURES	MEASURES	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
WERE	WERE	VBD	B-VP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
PLACE	PLACE	NN	B-NP	O
BEFORE	BEFORE	IN	B-PP	O
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
SINGLE	SINGLE	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
U.S.	U.S.	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
DEATH	DEATH	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OCCURRED	OCCURRED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
find	find	VBP	B-VP	O
out	out	RP	I-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
made	make	VBD	B-VP	O
TikTok	TikTok	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
AND	AND	CC	O	O
brought	bring	VBD	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
l	l	NNP	I-NP	O
'll	will	MD	B-VP	O
never	never	RB	B-ADVP	O
forgive	forgive	VB	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	NNPS	I-NP	B-MISC
!	!	.	O	O
				
RELEASE	RELEASE	VB	B-VP	B-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
VACCINE	VACCINE	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
WHAT	WHAT	WDT	B-NP	I-ORG
ABOUT	ABOUT	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
PHASE	PHASE	NN	B-NP	I-ORG
3	3	CD	I-NP	O
TRIALS	TRIALS	NNS	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
SAID	SAID	VBD	B-VP	O
RELEASE	RELEASE	NNP	B-NP	O
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	O
imgflip.com	imgflip.com	NNP	I-NP	O
				
WHY	WHY	WRB	B-ADVP	O
DO	DO	VB	B-VP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	B-NP	O
ALWAYS	ALWAYS	NNP	I-NP	O
SIT	SIT	NNP	I-NP	O
WAY	WAY	NNP	I-NP	O
OVER	OVER	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
THERE	THERE	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
?	?	.	O	O
				
SOCIAL	SOCIAL	JJ	B-NP	O
DISTANCING	DISTANCING	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
BEST	BEST	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
COMMENTARY	COMMENTARY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
NEMES	NEMES	NNS	B-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
AND	AND	CC	O	O
HUMORRET	HUMORRET	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
PORIOTFOST	PORIOTFOST	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
US	US	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
				
Anatomy	anatomy	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Right-Wing	Right-Wing	NNP	I-NP	O
Meme	Meme	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Mother	Mother	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Jones	Jones	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
#	#	#	B-NP	O
PUBG	PUBG	NNP	I-NP	O
banned	ban	VBD	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
India	India	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
Meanwhile	Meanwhile	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
Indian	Indian	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Parents	Parents	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
be	be	VB	B-VP	O
Like	like	IN	B-PP	O
Aakhir	Aakhir	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Wo	Wo	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
din	din	FW	I-NP	O
aa	aa	FW	I-NP	O
hi	hi	FW	I-NP	O
gya	gya	FW	I-NP	O
				
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
BRITISH	BRITISH	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
SING'GOD	SING'GOD	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SAVE	SAVE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OUR	OUR	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
QUEEN	QUEEN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	O
QUEEN	QUEEN	NNP	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
LIVES	LIVE	VBZ	B-VP	O
93	93	CD	B-NP	O
YEARS	YEARS	NNS	I-NP	O
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	O
BRITISH	BRITISH	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
:	:	:	O	O
was	be	VBD	B-VP	O
not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
expecting	expect	VBG	B-VP	O
that	that	DT	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
T	T	NNP	B-NP	O
WEA	WEA	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
MASAJUST	MASAJUST	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
DY	DY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TRE	TRE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ATE	ATE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SHEEPLE	SHEEPLE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BE	BE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LIKE	LIKE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Ns	Ns	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
mask	mask	NN	I-NP	O
S	S	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
JUSTA	JUSTA	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Ye	Ye	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
junt	junt	NN	I-NP	O
an	an	DT	B-NP	O
experimental	experimental	JJ	I-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
MISLEADING	MISLEADING	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
ITS	ITS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
JUST	JUST	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
AVACCINE	AVACCINE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'	'	POS	I-NP	O
s	s	NNS	I-NP	O
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
an	an	DT	B-NP	O
implantable	implantable	JJ	I-NP	O
microchip	microchip	NN	I-NP	O
It	it	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
an	an	DT	B-NP	O
internment	internment	NN	I-NP	O
camp	camp	NN	I-NP	O
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	O
JUST	JUST	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
MICROCHIP	MICROCHIP	NNP	I-NP	O
				
DO	DO	VB	B-VP	O
N'T	N'T	RB	B-ADVP	O
HAVE	HAVE	VBP	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
SUICIDE	SUICIDE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
WEINSTEIN	WEINSTEIN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IF	IF	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THEY	THEY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BLAME	BLAME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
				
COVID-19	COVID-19	JJ	B-NP	O
rest	rest	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
TODAY	TODAY	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Messages	Message	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
this	this	DT	B-NP	O
group	group	NN	I-NP	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
secured	secure	VBN	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
end-to-end	end-to-end	JJ	B-NP	O
encryption	encryption	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Tap	tap	NN	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
more	more	JJR	B-NP	O
info.	info.	NN	I-NP	O
china	china	NN	I-NP	O
created	create	VBD	B-VP	O
Vrus	Vrus	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
china	china	NN	I-NP	O
added	add	VBD	B-VP	O
rest	rest	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
china	china	NN	I-NP	O
left	leave	VBD	B-VP	O
				
Ever	ever	RB	B-ADVP	O
wonder	wonder	VBP	B-VP	O
what	what	WP	B-NP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Extra	Extra	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
stands	stand	VBZ	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	O	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
Corona	Corona	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Extra	Extra	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
vo	vo	NN	I-NP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
THEFUNNYBEAVER.COM	THEFUNNYBEAVER.COM	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
WHEN	WHEN	WRB	B-ADVP	O
THAT	THAT	DT	B-NP	O
RUSSIAN	RUSSIAN	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
VACCINE	VACCINE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
KICKS	KICKS	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
imaflip.com	imaflip.com	NN	B-NP	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
get	get	VBP	B-VP	O
WARS	WARS	NNS	B-NP	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
first	first	JJ	I-NP	O
day	day	NN	I-NP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
breaks	break	VBZ	B-VP	O
out	out	RP	I-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Tam	Tam	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
speed	spee	VBD	B-VP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
meme	meme	NN	I-NP	O
#	#	#	I-NP	O
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Modiji	Modiji	NNP	I-NP	O
Covid-19	Covid-19	NNP	I-NP	O
Rula	Rula	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
diya	diya	FW	I-NP	O
na	na	FW	I-NP	O
bechaari	bechaari	FW	I-NP	O
ko	ko	FW	I-NP	O
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
IndianEXPRES	IndianEXPRES	NNPS	I-NP	B-ORG
				
nimo	nimo	FW	O	O
enimsaden	enimsaden	FW	O	O
-	-	:	O	O
Oct	Oct	NNP	B-NP	O
20	20	CD	I-NP	O
Unseen	unseen	JJ	I-NP	O
footage	footage	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
Boris	Boris	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Johnson	Johnson	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
offering	offer	VBG	B-VP	O
£8	£8	CD	B-NP	O
per	per	IN	B-PP	O
head	head	NN	B-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
Andy	Andy	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Burnham	Burnham	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
mcan	mcan	JJ	I-NP	O
bonel	bonel	NN	I-NP	O
lockdown	lockdown	NN	I-NP	O
Andy	Andy	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
What	what	WP	B-NP	I-PER
could	can	MD	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
cost	cost	VB	B-VP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
10	10	CD	B-NP	O
pounds	pound	NNS	I-NP	O
ta	ta	NN	I-NP	O
3	3	CD	I-NP	O
O	O	NN	I-NP	O
34	34	CD	I-NP	O
				
They	they	PRP	O	O
should	shall	MD	B-VP	O
first	first	RB	B-ADVP	O
test	test	VB	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
covid	covid	JJ	I-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
gov't	gov't	NN	B-NP	O
officials	official	NNS	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
If	if	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
safe	safe	JJ	B-AP	O
,	,	,	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
good	good	JJ	B-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
But	but	CC	O	O
if	if	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
die	die	VBP	B-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
country	country	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
safe	safe	JJ	B-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
H	H	NNP	B-NP	O
COVID	COVID	NNP	I-NP	O
man	man	NN	I-NP	O
relly	relly	RB	B-ADVP	O
carried	carry	VBN	B-VP	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
breath	breath	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
why	why	WRB	B-ADVP	O
aet	aet	FW	B-NP	O
hunaha	hunaha	FW	I-NP	O
na	na	FW	I-NP	O
thena	thena	FW	I-NP	O
Wy	Wy	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
de	de	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
•	•	SYM	O	O
MISLEADING	MISLEAD	VBG	B-VP	O
wryback	wryback	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	O	O
your	your	PRP$	O	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Wake	Wake	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
up	up	IN	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
ETE	ETE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
VRAS	VRAS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	I-ORG
SPREADKADROEF	SPREADKADROEF	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
SALA	SALA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
TNELE	TNELE	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
ORP	ORP	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	I-MISC
SALNA	SALNA	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC
CAN	CAN	MD	B-VP	I-MISC
INFECT	INFECT	VB	I-VP	I-MISC
AN	AN	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
ENTRECITE	ENTRECITE	NN	I-NP	I-MISC
.	.	.	O	O
				
EKR	EKR	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
HEA	HEA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TORLE	TORLE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THETSAMPLE	THETSAMPLE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
				
Trung	Trung	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
says	say	VBZ	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
viras	vira	NNS	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
uka	uka	FW	B-NP	O
Covid	Covid	NNP	I-NP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
know	know	VBP	B-VP	O
more	much	RBR	B-ADVP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
wind	wind	NN	B-NP	O
than	than	IN	B-PP	O
yourdo.	yourdo.	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
took	take	VBD	B-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
peraonaly	peraonaly	RB	B-NP	O
Cape	Cape	NNP	I-NP	O
y	y	NN	I-NP	O
e	e	FW	I-NP	O
pa	pa	FW	I-NP	O
nd	nd	FW	I-NP	O
aa	aa	FW	I-NP	O
				
WE	WE	PRP	O	O
ARE	ARE	VBP	B-VP	B-ORG
NOT	NOT	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
EAT	EAT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TOFU	TOFU	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SCARED	SCARED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
YET.	YET.	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
dumb	dumb	JJ	I-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
years	year	NNS	I-NP	O
from	from	IN	O	O
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
:	:	:	O	O
THAT	THAT	IN	B-PP	O
WHOLE	WHOLE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THING	THING	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WAS	WAS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OVERHYPED	OVERHYPED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
DID	DID	VBD	B-VP	O
N'T	N'T	RB	B-ADVP	B-MISC
EVEN	EVEN	RB	I-ADVP	I-MISC
DIE	DIE	VB	B-VP	I-MISC
!	!	.	O	O
				
Norton	Norton	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
AntiVirus	AntiVirus	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Proci	Proci	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
Whole	whole	JJ	B-NP	O
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
Putin	Putin	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
*	*	SYM	O	O
Putin	Putin	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Vaccine	Vaccine	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Well	Well	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
done	do	VBN	B-VP	O
putinsimso	putinsimso	NN	B-NP	O
proud	proud	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
you	you	PRP	B-NP	O
Vaccine	Vaccine	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Vaccine	Vaccine	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
joking	joke	VBG	B-VP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
happening	happen	VBG	B-VP	O
new	new	JJ	B-NP	O
disease	disease	NN	I-NP	O
starts	start	VBZ	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
china	china	NN	B-NP	O
				
futuristic	futuristic	JJ	B-NP	O
caveman	caveman	NN	I-NP	O
@	@	IN	B-PP	O
uturisticcavet	uturisticcavet	JJ	B-NP	O
10h	10h	JJ	I-NP	O
Boris	Boris	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Johnson	Johnson	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
reaction	reaction	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
covid-19	covid-19	JJ	B-NP	O
seifisolating	seifisolating	NN	I-NP	O
Ojust	Ojust	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
feel	feel	VBP	B-VP	O
that	that	IN	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
yknow	yknow	NN	B-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
if	if	IN	B-PP	O
itaint	itaint	NN	B-NP	O
broke	break	VBD	B-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
fix	fix	VB	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
And	and	CC	O	O
even	even	RB	B-ADVP	O
if	if	IN	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
broke	broke	JJ	B-AP	O
,	,	,	O	O
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
ignore	ignore	VB	B-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
and	and	CC	O	O
maybe	maybe	RB	B-ADVP	O
it'l	it'l	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
sort	sort	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	O	O
..	..	.	O	O
okay	okay	NN	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
GIF	GIF	NN	B-NP	B-ORG
				
Indian	Indian	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC
8	8	CD	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
G	G	NNP	B-NP	O
Curana	Curana	NNP	I-NP	O
Go	Go	NNP	I-NP	O
Yesterday	Yesterday	NNP	I-NP	O
Rekha	Rekha	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Jis	Jis	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Socurty	Socurty	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Guard	Guard	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
tested	test	VBD	B-VP	O
COVID	COVID	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
postive	postive	VBP	B-VP	O
Now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
,	,	,	O	O
Amit	Amit	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
ji	jus	NNS	I-NP	O
tosted	tost	VBD	B-VP	O
COVD	COVD	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
positivatiekhatAmitateBachan	positivatiekhatAmitateBachan	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Aap	Aap	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
chronology	chronology	NN	I-NP	O
samajhiye	samajhiye	NN	I-NP	O
Om	Om	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
1203	1203	CD	I-NP	O
AM	AM	NNP	I-NP	O
-	-	:	O	O
Ja	Ja	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
12	12	CD	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
200	200	CD	B-NP	O
O20	O20	CD	I-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
talng	talng	JJ	B-NP	O
atout	atout	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
				
RELEASE	RELEASE	VB	B-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
VACCINE	VACCINE	NN	I-NP	B-MISC
WHAT	WHAT	WDT	B-NP	I-MISC
ABOUT	ABOUT	IN	B-PP	I-MISC
PHASE3	PHASE3	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC
TRIALS	TRIALS	NNS	I-NP	I-MISC
?	?	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
SAID	SAID	VBD	B-VP	O
RELEASE	RELEASE	VB	I-VP	O
IT	IT	PRP	O	O
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
suffering	suffer	VBG	B-VP	O
from	from	IN	O	O
'	'	``	O	O
Hanta	Hanta	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
'	'	''	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
originated	originate	VBD	B-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
Rodents	rodent	NNS	B-NP	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
HAVE	HAVE	VBP	B-VP	O
CORONA	CORONA	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
•	•	LS	O	O
NO	NO	DT	B-NP	O
EVIDENCE	EVIDENCE	NNP	I-NP	O
Vlaimir	Vlaimir	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Putin	Putin	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
isOsharing	isOshare	VBG	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
COvo-19	COvo-19	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Update	Update	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
.	.	.	O	O
				
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
first	first	JJ	I-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
aganat	aganat	IN	B-PP	O
coronavirus	coronavirus	NN	B-NP	O
wil	wil	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
segissered	segisser	VBN	I-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
Russia	Russia	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
few	few	JJ	I-NP	O
days	day	NNS	I-NP	O
usian	usian	JJ	I-NP	O
scientints	scientint	NNS	I-NP	O
passed	pass	VBD	B-VP	O
necessary	necessary	JJ	B-NP	O
test	test	NN	I-NP	O
stages	stage	NNS	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
proved	prove	VBD	B-VP	O
1the	1the	JJ	B-NP	O
salety	salety	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
etfectiveness	etfectiveness	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
drug	drug	NN	I-NP	O
Cur	Cur	NNP	I-NP	O
medione	medione	NN	I-NP	O
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
adequately	adequately	RB	B-ADVP	O
coped	cope	VBN	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
epidemic	epidemic	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
gives	give	VBZ	B-VP	O
hope	hope	NN	B-NP	O
not	not	RB	B-NP	O
only	only	RB	I-NP	O
0	0	CD	I-NP	O
our	our	PRP$	B-NP	O
country	country	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
but	but	CC	O	O
10	10	CD	B-NP	O
he	he	PRP	B-NP	O
whole	whole	JJ	I-NP	O
warld	warld	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Once	once	RB	B-ADVP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Soviet	Soviet	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
satelite	satelite	NN	I-NP	O
prved	prve	VBD	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
way	way	NN	I-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
humarity	humarity	NN	B-NP	O
inno	inno	NN	I-NP	O
space	space	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Russian	Russian	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
wil	wil	MD	B-VP	O
pave	pave	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
wiy	wiy	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
uture	uture	NN	I-NP	O
without	without	IN	B-PP	O
COVID-19	COVID-19	NN	B-NP	O
masks	mask	NNS	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
social	social	JJ	B-NP	O
solation	solation	NN	I-NP	O
				
5	5	CD	B-NP	O
11	11	CD	I-NP	O
2019	2019	CD	I-NP	O
USA	USA	NNP	I-NP	O
President	President	NNP	I-NP	O
taen	taen	NN	I-NP	O
il	il	IN	B-PP	O
Global	Global	NNP	B-NP	O
e	e	NNP	I-NP	O
News	News	NNP	I-NP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
ehte	ehte	NN	I-NP	O
tetie	tetie	NN	I-NP	O
Infected	Infected	NNP	I-NP	O
Morld	Morld	NNP	I-NP	O
Dead	Dead	NNP	I-NP	O
1.220.2,74B	1.220.2,74B	NNP	I-NP	O
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
simulations	simulation	NNS	I-NP	O
				
BREAKING	BREAKING	NN	B-NP	O
•	•	SYM	O	O
3	3	CD	B-NP	O
HRS	HRS	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
SCREENRANT.COM	SCREENRANT.COM	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Tom	Tom	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Hanks	Hanks	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'	'	POS	I-NP	O
Blood	Blood	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Being	Being	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Used	use	VBN	B-VP	I-PER
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
Develop	Develop	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
COVID	COVID	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Vaccine	Vaccine	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
P	P	NNP	I-NP	O
'll	will	MD	B-VP	O
finally	finally	RB	B-ADVP	O
have	have	VB	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
friend	friend	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	O	O
me	me	PRP	O	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
can	can	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
contracted	contract	VBN	I-VP	O
only	only	RB	B-ADVP	O
through	through	IN	B-PP	O
human	human	JJ	B-NP	O
contact	contact	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Introverts	introvert	NNS	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
				
People	people	NNS	B-NP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
normal	normal	JJ	B-NP	O
flu	flu	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
where	where	WRB	B-ADVP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
'm	be	VBP	B-VP	O
staying	stay	VBG	I-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
home	home	NN	I-NP	O
People	people	NNS	I-NP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
travel	travel	VBP	B-VP	O
all	all	DT	O	O
around	around	IN	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
city	city	NN	I-NP	O
Golinand	Golinand	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
out	out	IN	O	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
locometivesoim	locometivesoim	NN	B-NP	O
				
Say	say	VB	B-VP	O
no	no	DT	O	O
to	to	TO	O	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
torona	torona	NNP	I-NP	O
Light	Light	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
TSINGTAO	TSINGTAO	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
AERS	AERS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
They	they	PRP	O	O
should	shall	MD	B-VP	O
first	first	RB	B-ADVP	O
test	test	VB	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
covid	covid	JJ	I-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
gov't	gov't	NN	B-NP	O
officials	official	NNS	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
If	if	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
safe	safe	JJ	B-AP	O
,	,	,	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
good	good	JJ	B-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
But	but	CC	O	O
if	if	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
die	die	VBP	B-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
country	country	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
safe	safe	JJ	B-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
because	because	IN	B-PP	O
thousands	thousand	NNS	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
FALSE	FALSE	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
independent	independent	JJ	I-NP	O
Doctors	doctor	NNS	I-NP	O
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
saying	say	VBG	I-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
Hydrocyhloroquine	Hydrocyhloroquine	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
cures	cure	VBZ	B-VP	O
all	all	DT	B-NP	O
CV-19	CV-19	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
patients	patient	NNS	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
It	it	PRP	O	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
not	not	RB	B-AP	O
valid	valid	JJ	I-AP	O
until	until	IN	O	O
we	we	PRP	O	O
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
major	major	JJ	I-NP	O
study	study	NN	I-NP	O
done	do	VBN	B-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
As	as	RB	B-ADVP	O
soon	soon	RB	I-ADVP	O
as	as	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
CV-19	CV-19	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Vaceine	Vaceine	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
manufactured	manufacture	VBN	I-VP	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
must	must	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
immediately	immediately	RB	B-ADVP	O
delivered	deliver	VBN	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
health	health	NN	B-NP	O
care	care	NN	I-NP	O
professionals	professional	NNS	I-NP	O
world	world	NN	I-NP	O
wide	wide	JJ	B-AP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
immediate	immediate	JJ	B-NP	O
human	human	JJ	I-NP	O
injection	injection	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
:	:	:	O	O
				
Proper	proper	JJ	B-NP	O
studies	study	NNS	I-NP	O
can	can	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
performed	perform	VBN	I-VP	O
later	later	RB	B-ADVP	O
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
You	you	PRP	O	O
think	think	VBP	B-VP	O
this	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
funny	funny	JJ	B-AP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
Reddit	reddit	VB	B-VP	O
making	make	VBG	I-VP	O
memes	meme	NNS	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
				
Funny	Funny	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Memes	Memes	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
The	The	NNP	I-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
wo	will	MD	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
last	last	VB	B-VP	O
long	long	RB	B-ADVP	O
because	because	IN	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
was	be	VBD	B-VP	O
made	make	VBN	I-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
SHAFS	SHAFS	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
1820	1820	CD	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
1920	1920	CD	B-NP	O
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
disease	disease	NN	B-NP	O
outbreaks	outbreak	NNS	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
hear	hear	VBP	B-VP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
epidemic	epidemic	NN	I-NP	O
				
Twitter	Twitter	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Safety	Safety	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TwitterSa	TwitterSa	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
·	·	SYM	O	O
2h	2h	CD	B-NP	O
In	in	IN	B-PP	O
addition	addition	NN	B-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
we	we	PRP	O	O
will	will	MD	B-VP	O
:	:	:	O	O
1	1	CD	B-NP	O
No	no	RB	I-NP	O
longer	long	RBR	I-NP	O
serve	serve	VB	B-VP	O
content	content	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
accounts	account	NNS	B-NP	O
associated	associate	VBN	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
QAnon	QAnon	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
Trends	Trend	NNPS	B-NP	B-LOC
and	and	CC	O	O
recommendations	recommendation	NNS	B-NP	O
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
Work	work	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
ensure	ensure	VB	I-VP	O
we	we	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
highlighting	highlight	VBG	B-VP	O
this	this	DT	B-NP	O
activity	activity	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
search	search	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
conversations	conversation	NNS	B-NP	O
3	3	CD	I-NP	O
Block	Block	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
URLS	URLS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
associated	associate	VBN	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
QAnon	QAnon	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
from	from	IN	B-VP	O
being	be	VBG	I-VP	O
shared	share	VBN	I-VP	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
Twitter	Twitter	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
GANONS	GANONS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WE	WE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NEED	NEED	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	NNP	I-NP	O
DIG	DIG	NNP	I-NP	O
DEEPER	DEEPER	NNP	I-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
beshram	beshram	NN	B-NP	O
memer	memer	NN	I-NP	O
Obeshram_memer	Obeshram_memer	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
After	After	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
successfully	successfully	RB	B-NP	O
human	human	JJ	I-NP	O
trial	trial	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
#	#	#	B-NP	O
coronavaccine	coronavaccine	NN	I-NP	O
by	by	IN	B-PP	O
russia	russia	NN	B-NP	O
Putin	Putin	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
and	and	CC	O	O
scientists	scientist	NNS	B-NP	O
research	research	NN	I-NP	O
team	team	NN	I-NP	O
be	be	VB	B-VP	O
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
#	#	#	B-NP	O
RussianVaccine	RussianVaccine	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
				
roz	roz	FW	O	O
subah	subah	FW	O	O
utho	utho	FW	O	O
nahao	nahao	FW	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
china	china	FW	O	O
se	se	FW	O	O
aayi	aayi	FW	O	O
nayi	nayi	FW	O	O
virus	virus	FW	O	O
ke	ke	FW	O	O
bare	bare	FW	O	O
meln	meln	FW	O	O
padho	padho	FW	O	O
or	or	FW	O	O
soo	soo	FW	O	O
jao	jao	FW	O	O
				
John	John	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Fugelsang	Fugelsang	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
@	@	NNP	I-NP	O
JohnFugelsang	JohnFugelsang	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Well	Well	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
I	I	PRP	O	O
'm	be	VBP	B-VP	O
not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
surprised	surprise	VBN	B-VP	O
Trump	Trump	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
tested	test	VBD	B-VP	O
positive	positive	JJ	B-AP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
Covid	Covid	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
-	-	:	O	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
guy	guy	NN	I-NP	O
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
5	5	CD	B-NP	O
major	major	JJ	I-NP	O
risk	risk	NN	I-NP	O
groups	group	NNS	I-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
1	1	LS	O	O
)	)	)	O	O
He	he	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
elderly	elderly	JJ	B-NP	O
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
)	)	)	O	O
He	he	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
obese	obese	JJ	B-NP	O
3	3	CD	I-NP	O
)	)	)	O	O
He	he	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
got	get	VBD	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
public	public	JJ	I-NP	O
sector	sector	NN	I-NP	O
job	job	NN	I-NP	O
4	4	CD	I-NP	O
)	)	)	O	O
He	he	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
person	person	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
color	color	NN	B-NP	O
5	5	CD	I-NP	O
)	)	)	O	O
He	he	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
poor	poor	JJ	B-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
#	#	#	B-NP	O
PrayForTrump	PrayForTrump	NNP	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-NP	O
#	#	#	I-NP	O
WearADamnMask	WearADamnMask	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
				
1720,1820,and	1720,1820,and	CD	B-NP	O
1920	1920	CD	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Have	have	VB	B-VP	O
massive	massive	JJ	B-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
outbreaks	outbreak	NNS	I-NP	O
Not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
even	even	RB	I-ADVP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
month	month	NN	I-NP	O
into	into	IN	B-PP	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Worid	worid	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG
news	news	NN	I-NP	O
Tarker	Tarker	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
tody	tody	NN	I-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
'	'	``	O	O
mysterious	mysterious	JJ	B-AP	O
'	'	''	O	O
virus	virus	NN	B-NP	O
outbreak	outbreak	NN	I-NP	O
grows	grow	VBZ	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
139	139	CD	B-NP	O
cases	case	NNS	I-NP	O
reported	report	VBN	B-VP	O
over	over	IN	B-NP	O
two	two	CD	I-NP	O
days	day	NNS	I-NP	O
Im	im	VBP	B-VP	O
beginning	begin	VBG	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
see	see	VB	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
pattern	pattern	NN	I-NP	O
here	here	RB	B-ADVP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
im	im	PRP	B-NP	O
not	not	RB	I-NP	O
so	so	RB	I-NP	O
sure	sure	JJ	I-NP	O
i	us	NNS	I-NP	O
like	like	IN	I-NP	O
				
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
spreads	spread	VBZ	B-VP	O
Me	me	PRP	O	O
realizing	realize	VBG	B-VP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
shirt	shirt	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
made	make	VBN	I-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
GET	GET	VB	B-VP	O
THIS	THIS	DT	B-NP	O
SIT	SIT	NN	I-NP	O
OFF	OFF	IN	O	O
ME	ME	PRP	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
1华人只共和	1华人只共和	LS	O	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
W	W	NNP	I-NP	O
SE	SE	NNP	I-NP	O
inistr	inistr	NN	I-NP	O
Fore	Fore	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
WA	WA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ANGERS	ANGERS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WITH	WITH	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'	'	POS	I-NP	O
CHINESE	CHINESE	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
TWEET	TWEET	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
THIS	THIS	DT	B-VP	O
IS	I	VBZ	I-VP	O
DONALD	DONALD	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	O
FACE	FACE	NNP	I-NP	O
UNDER	UNDER	NNP	I-NP	O
HIS	HIS	NNP	I-NP	O
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	O
imgtip.com	imgtip.com	NN	I-NP	O
				
PLAY	PLAY	NNP	B-NP	O
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
SAFE	SAFE	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
DO	DO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
N'T	N'T	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WORRY	WORRY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LEAVE	LEAVE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OUR	OUR	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BORDERS	BORDERS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ОPEN	ОPEN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
COTE	COTE	NNP	I-NP	O
SHUT	SHUT	NNP	I-NP	O
OUR	OUR	NNP	I-NP	O
BORDERS	BORDERS	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	NNP	I-NP	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	O
NOW	NOW	RB	B-NP	O
98	98	CD	I-NP	O
%	%	NN	I-NP	O
LEAVE	LEAVE	NNP	I-NP	O
THEM	THEM	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
OPEN	OPEN	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
CLOSE	CLOSE	NNP	I-NP	O
THEM	THEM	NNP	I-NP	O
NOw	NOw	NNP	I-NP	O
This	this	DT	B-NP	O
poll	poll	NN	I-NP	O
has	have	VBZ	B-VP	O
ended	end	VBN	I-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
33.8K	33.8K	CD	B-NP	O
Votes	vote	NNS	I-NP	O
				
SPREAD	SPREAD	NN	B-NP	O
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	O
DEADLY	DEADLY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Map	Map	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
reveals	reveal	VBZ	B-VP	O
spread	spread	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
killer	killer	NN	B-NP	O
bug	bug	NN	I-NP	O
Making	make	VBG	B-VP	O
memes	meme	NNS	B-NP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
S.KOREA	S.KOREA	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
CASE	CASE	NN	I-NP	O
471	471	CD	I-NP	O
CASES	CASES	NNS	I-NP	O
17	17	CD	I-NP	O
DEATHS	DEATHS	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
JAPAN	JAPAN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
CASE	CASE	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
USA	USA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
CASE	CASE	NN	I-NP	O
getting	get	VBG	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
TAIWAN	TAIWAN	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
CASE	CASE	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
HONG	HONG	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
KONG	KONG	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
2	2	CD	I-NP	O
CASES	CASES	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
MEXICO	MEXICO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
UNCONFIRMED	UNCONFIRMED	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
THAILAND	THAILAND	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
4	4	CD	I-NP	O
CASES	CASES	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
MACAU	MACAU	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
CASE	CASE	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
AUSTRALIA	AUSTRALIA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
SUSPECTED	SUSPECT	VBN	B-VP	B-ORG
CASE	CASE	NN	B-NP	I-ORG
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
now	now	RB	B-ADVP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
US	US	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
screwd	screwd	NN	I-NP	O
				
THEY	THEY	PRP	O	O
SAY	SAY	VBP	B-VP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	B-MISC
SHOULD	SHOULD	MD	B-VP	I-MISC
WEAR	WEAR	VB	I-VP	I-MISC
A	A	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
.	.	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
DO	DO	VBP	B-VP	O
N'T	N'T	RB	B-ADVP	B-MISC
NEED	NEED	VB	B-VP	I-MISC
A	A	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
.	.	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
'M	'M	VBP	B-VP	O
HEALTHY	HEALTHY	NNP	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
GREAT	GREAT	JJ	B-AP	O
-	-	:	O	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
COVIDIOTS	COVIDIOTS	NNS	I-NP	O
HEARD	HEARD	VBP	B-VP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
				
RUN	RUN	VB	B-VP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
GODZILLA	GODZILLA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	I-ORG
ATTACKING	ATTACK	VBG	B-VP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
CITY	CITY	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
RELAX	RELAX	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
HE	HE	PRP	O	O
'S	'	VBZ	B-VP	O
ONLY	ONLY	RB	B-ADVP	O
KILLED	KILL	VBN	B-VP	O
4000	4000	CD	B-NP	O
PEOPLE	PEOPLE	NNS	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
FLU	FLU	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
KILLS	KILLS	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG
OVER	OVER	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
25,000	25,000	CD	B-NP	O
EVERY	EVERY	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
YÉAR	YÉAR	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
!	!	.	O	O
				
Posted	post	VBN	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
r	r	NN	B-NP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
funny	funny	JJ	B-AP	O
by	by	IN	O	O
u	u	JJ	B-AP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
Trippy_Styx666	Trippy_Styx666	NNP	B-NP	O
O	O	NNP	I-NP	O
reddit	reddit	NN	I-NP	O
				
Bors	Bors	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Aohons	Aohons	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Con	Con	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
potey	potey	NN	I-NP	O
Soma	soma	NN	I-NP	O
alyou	alyou	NN	I-NP	O
may	may	MD	B-VP	O
đ	đ	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
.	.	.	O	O
				
We	we	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
meant	mean	VBN	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
die	die	VB	I-VP	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
dimate	dimate	JJ	B-NP	O
change	change	NN	I-NP	O
10	10	CD	I-NP	O
make	make	VBP	B-VP	O
Assie	Assie	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Stuff	Stuff	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
Aucsies	aucsy	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG
				
RUSSIA	RUSSIA	NNP	B-NP	O
REGISTERS	REGISTERS	NNP	I-NP	O
1ST	1ST	NNP	I-NP	O
CORONAVIRUSVACCINE	CORONAVIRUSVACCINE	NNP	I-NP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
WORLD	WORLD	NNP	I-NP	O
U.S.	U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
HOSES	HOSES	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
DOWN	DOWN	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
RUSSIAN	RUSSIAN	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
VACCINE	VACCINE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
AND	AND	CC	O	I-MISC
SAYS	SAY	VBZ	B-VP	I-MISC
IT	IT	PRP	O	I-MISC
WILL	WILL	MD	B-VP	I-MISC
HAVE	HAVE	VB	I-VP	I-MISC
MILLIONS	MILLIONS	NNS	B-NP	I-MISC
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	I-MISC
DOSES	DOSES	NNS	B-NP	I-MISC
READY	READY	JJ	I-NP	I-MISC
YEAR	YEAR	NN	I-NP	O
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	O
END	END	NN	I-NP	O
imgflip.com	imgflip.com	NN	I-NP	O
				
January	January	NNP	B-NP	O
February	February	NNP	I-NP	O
March	March	NNP	I-NP	O
April	April	NNP	I-NP	O
May	May	NNP	I-NP	O
July	July	NNP	I-NP	O
				
After	after	IN	B-PP	O
quarantine	quarantine	NN	B-NP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
will	will	MD	B-VP	O
either	either	CC	O	O
look	look	VB	B-VP	O
like	like	IN	O	O
:	:	:	O	O
You	you	PRP	O	O
want	want	VBP	B-VP	O
eat	eat	VB	I-VP	O
up	up	RP	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Ponos	Ponos	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
You	you	PRP	O	I-MISC
want	want	VBP	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	O	O
OR	OR	CC	O	O
beat	beat	VB	B-VP	O
up	up	RP	I-VP	O
Thanos	thano	NNS	B-NP	O
othegoanyao	othegoanyao	RB	B-ADVP	O
				
Chinese	Chinese	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC
virologist	virologist	NN	I-NP	O
Dr	Dr	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Li-Meng	Li-Meng	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Yan	Yan	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'	'	POS	I-NP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
created	create	VBD	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
govt	govt	NN	I-NP	O
lab	lab	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
Wuhan	Wuhan	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
'	'	''	O	O
says	say	VBZ	B-VP	O
whistleblower	whistleblow	JJR	B-NP	O
COMEDY	COMEDY	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
AAAAND	AAAAND	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SHE	SHE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	I-ORG
GONE	GONE	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
HAPPEN	HAPPEN	VBP	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
THINK	THINK	VB	I-VP	O
FAUCI	FAUCI	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
GREAT	GREAT	NNP	I-NP	O
GUY	GUY	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
ON	ON	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
OTHER	OTHER	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
HAND	HAND	NN	I-NP	I-MISC
,	,	,	O	O
HE	HE	PRP	O	B-ORG
CHANGED	CHANG	VBD	B-VP	I-ORG
HIS	HIS	PRP$	B-NP	I-ORG
MIND	MIND	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
ABOUT	ABOUT	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
MASKSI	MASKSI	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
BUT	BUT	CC	O	I-ORG
WHEN	WHEN	WRB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	I-ORG
THINK	THINK	VBP	B-VP	I-ORG
ABOUT	ABOUT	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
VOTERS	VOTERS	NNS	B-NP	B-MISC
MIGHT	MIGHT	MD	B-VP	I-MISC
LIKE	LIKE	VB	I-VP	I-MISC
A	A	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
NICE	NICE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
...	...	:	O	O
				
WELL	WELL	RB	B-ADVP	O
REASONED	REASON	VBN	B-VP	O
				
ITOOK	ITOOK	VB	B-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
LIBERTY	LIBERTY	NN	I-NP	O
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	O
BULLSHITTIN	BULLSHITTIN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
YAL	YAL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
习近筆	习近筆	NN	I-NP	O
ANDYOU	ANDYOU	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
SAY.RIAR	SAY.RIAR	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
RIAR	RIAR	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
PANTS	PANTS	NNS	I-NP	O
ON	ON	IN	B-PP	O
FIRE	FIRE	NN	B-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
THINK	THINK	VBP	B-VP	B-ORG
ILOOK	ILOOK	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
GOOD	GOOD	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WEARING	WEARING	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
JUST	JUST	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LIKE	LIKE	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
LONE	LONE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
RANGER	RANGER	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
US	US	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
:	:	:	O	O
Suffocating	suffocate	VBG	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
masks	mask	NNS	B-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
times	time	NNS	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
KAKASHI	KAKASHI	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
:	:	:	O	O
Suffocating	suffocate	VBG	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
masks	mask	NNS	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
his	his	PRP$	B-NP	O
entire	entire	JJ	I-NP	O
life	life	NN	I-NP	O
				
extroverts	extrovert	NNS	B-NP	O
outside	outside	IN	O	O
armed	arm	VBN	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
masks	mask	NNS	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
hand	hand	NN	B-NP	O
sanitizer	sanitizer	NN	I-NP	O
constantly	constantly	RB	B-ADVP	O
taking	take	VBG	B-VP	O
risks	risk	NNS	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
contracting	contracting	NN	B-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
spreading	spread	VBG	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
CDC	CDC	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
introverts	introvert	NNS	I-NP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
crippling	crippling	JJ	B-NP	O
depression	depression	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
social	social	JJ	B-NP	O
anxiety	anxiety	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
already	already	RB	B-ADVP	O
barricaded	barricade	VBN	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
their	their	PRP$	B-NP	O
home	home	NN	I-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
months	month	NNS	B-NP	O
prior	prior	RB	B-ADVP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
first	first	JJ	I-NP	O
outbreak	outbreak	NN	I-NP	O
AIR	AIR	NN	I-NP	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
out	out	IN	O	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
toilet	toilet	NN	B-NP	O
paper	paper	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
but	but	CC	O	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
kitten	kitten	NN	I-NP	O
walks	walk	VBZ	B-VP	O
into	into	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
room	room	NN	I-NP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
'm	be	VBP	B-VP	O
sorry	sorry	JJ	B-AP	O
,	,	,	O	O
little	little	JJ	B-NP	O
one	one	CD	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
HEART	HEART	NN	B-NP	O
DISEASE	DISEASE	NN	I-NP	O
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
NUMBER	NUMBER	NN	I-NP	B-MISC
ONE	ONE	CD	I-NP	I-MISC
CAUSE	CAUSE	NN	I-NP	I-MISC
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	I-MISC
DEATH	DEATH	NN	B-NP	I-MISC
,	,	,	O	O
DID	DID	VBD	B-VP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
KNOW	KNOW	VBP	B-VP	O
THAT	THAT	DT	O	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
THATS	THATS	NNS	B-NP	O
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
BADGE	BADGE	NN	I-NP	O
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	O
HONOR	HONOR	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
BECAUSE	BECAUSE	IN	O	O
WE	WE	PRP	O	O
WILL	WILL	MD	B-VP	O
BEAT	BEAT	VB	I-VP	O
THAT	THAT	DT	O	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
BELIEVE	BELIEVE	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
ME	ME	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
on	on	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
crowded	crowded	JJ	I-NP	O
MRT	MRT	NNP	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
someone	someone	NN	B-NP	O
starts	start	VBZ	B-VP	O
coughing	cough	VBG	I-VP	O
				
EVERYBODY	EVERYBODY	NN	B-NP	O
HATES	HATE	VBZ	B-VP	O
ON	ON	IN	B-PP	O
SUPPLY	SUPPLY	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
UNTILDE	UNTILDE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
CORONA	CORONA	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
STRIKES	STRIKES	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
				
States	state	NNS	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Alright	alright	RB	B-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
We	we	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
going	go	VBG	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
open	open	VB	I-VP	O
back	back	RB	B-ADVP	O
up	up	RB	I-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
COVID-19	COVID-19	NN	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
jongaldbeng	jongaldbeng	NN	B-NP	O
				
Over	over	IN	B-PP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
dead	dead	JJ	I-NP	O
body	body	NN	I-NP	O
will	will	MD	B-VP	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
get	get	VB	B-VP	O
me	me	PRP	O	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
take	take	VB	I-VP	O
that	that	DT	B-NP	O
vaccine	vaccine	NN	I-NP	O
				
HOPE	HOPE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
THEY	THEY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ALLOW	ALLOW	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
US	US	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OFF	OFF	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LOCKDOWN	LOCKDOWN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BYJULY	BYJULY	NNP	I-NP	O
4TH	4TH	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
SO	SO	RB	B-ADVP	O
WE	WE	PRP	O	O
CAN	CAN	MD	B-VP	B-MISC
CELEBRATE	CELEBRATE	VB	I-VP	I-MISC
OUR	OUR	PRP$	B-NP	I-MISC
FREEDOM	FREEDOM	NN	I-NP	I-MISC
.	.	.	O	O
				
IMPEACHES	IMPEACHE	VBZ	B-VP	B-LOC
USA	USA	NNP	B-NP	I-LOC
				
NONT	NONT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
ASK	ASK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
RE	RE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ASK	ASK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
FIRST	FIRST	NNP	B-NP	O
DAY	DAY	NNP	I-NP	O
BACK	BACK	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
SCHOOL	SCHOOL	NNP	B-NP	O
AFTER	AFTER	NNP	I-NP	O
LOCKDOWN	LOCKDOWN	NNP	I-NP	O
VISIT	VISIT	NNP	I-NP	O
PATRIOTPO0ST.US	PATRIOTPO0ST.US	NNP	I-NP	O
FOR	FOR	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
BEST	B	JJS	I-NP	O
HUMOR	HUMOR	NN	I-NP	O
AND	AND	CC	O	O
MEMES	MEMES	NNS	B-NP	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
did	do	VBD	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
even	even	RB	I-VP	O
realize	realize	VB	B-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
spent	spend	VBD	B-VP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
childhood	childhood	NN	I-NP	O
playing	play	VBG	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
...	...	:	O	O
				
Captain	Captain	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
America	America	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
after	after	IN	B-VP	O
wielding	wield	VBG	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Mjolnire	Mjolnire	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Outsides	Outsides	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
				
Were	be	VBD	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
nur	nur	PRP$	B-NP	O
tin	tin	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
deteat	deteat	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
w	w	NN	I-NP	O
s	s	NNS	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
rny	rny	JJ	B-NP	O
peopie	peopie	NNS	I-NP	O
say	say	VBP	B-VP	O
tat	tat	NN	B-NP	O
ict	ict	NN	I-NP	O
veera	veera	NN	I-NP	O
tace	tace	NN	I-NP	O
k	k	NN	I-NP	O
whes	whe	VBZ	B-VP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
tance	tance	VBP	B-VP	O
There	there	EX	O	O
k	k	NN	B-NP	O
nolody	nolody	NN	I-NP	O
o	o	NN	I-NP	O
Paiote	paiote	VB	B-VP	O
me	me	PRP	B-PP	O
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
vesitent	vesitent	NN	I-NP	O
YEAH	YEAH	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
THIS	THIS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	O
BIG	BIG	NNP	B-NP	O
GRAIN	GRAIN	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
TIME	TIME	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
Waiting	wait	VBG	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
laua	laua	NN	I-NP	O
like	like	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Swede	Swede	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Before	Before	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
During	During	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
CNN	CNN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Reporter	Reporter	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Who	Who	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Attacked	Attacked	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
For	for	IN	O	I-ORG
Not	not	RB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
Wearing	wear	VBG	B-VP	I-ORG
Mask	Mask	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
Caught	Caught	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Removing	Removing	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Mask	Mask	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
When	When	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Cameras	Cameras	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Stop	Stop	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Rolling	Rolling	NNP	I-NP	O
Hа	Hа	NNP	I-NP	O
На	На	NNP	I-NP	O
На	На	NNP	I-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
Steve	Steve	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
King	King	NNP	I-NP	O
...	...	:	O	O
				
4	4	CD	B-NP	O
hrs	hr	NNS	I-NP	O
·	·	VBP	B-VP	O
O	O	NNP	B-NP	O
ACCORDING	ACCORDING	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	NNP	I-NP	O
CNN	CNN	NNP	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
TOOK	TOOK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OBAMA	OBAMA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
MLLIONS	MLLIONS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
INFECTED	INFECTED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
AND	AND	CC	O	O
OVER	OVER	IN	B-PP	O
1,000	1,000	CD	B-NP	O
DEATHS	DEATHS	NNS	I-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
DECLARE	DECLARE	NNP	B-NP	O
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	O
HIN1	HIN1	NNP	I-NP	O
FLU	FLU	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
HEALTH	HEALTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EMERGENCY	EMERGENCY	NNP	I-NP	O
TURNING	TURNING	NNP	I-NP	O
PÕINT	PÕINT	NNP	I-NP	O
USA	USA	NNP	I-NP	O
UNDER	UNDER	NNP	I-NP	O
PRESIDENT	PRESIDENT	NNP	I-NP	O
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	O
WAS	WAS	NNP	I-NP	O
DECLARED	DECLARED	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
HEALTH	HEALTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EMERGENCY	EMERGENCY	NNP	I-NP	O
AND	AND	NNP	I-NP	O
PUBLIC	PUBLIC	NNP	I-NP	O
SAFETY	SAFETY	NNP	I-NP	O
MEASURES	MEASURES	NNP	I-NP	O
WERE	WERE	VBD	B-VP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
PLACE	PLACE	NNP	B-NP	O
BEFORE	BEFORE	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
SINGLE	SINGLE	NNP	I-NP	O
U.S.	U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
DEATH	DEATH	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
OCCURRED	OCCURR	VBD	B-VP	I-ORG
1.6K	1.6K	CD	B-NP	O
269	269	CD	I-NP	O
Comments	Comments	NNP	I-NP	O
1K	1K	NNP	I-NP	O
Shares	Share	NNPS	I-NP	O
				
Week	week	NN	B-NP	O
4	4	CD	I-NP	O
Week	week	NN	I-NP	O
10	10	CD	I-NP	O
				
Answer	answer	NN	B-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
all	all	DT	B-NP	O
questions	question	NNS	I-NP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
coming	come	VBG	I-NP	O
school	school	NN	I-NP	O
year	year	NN	I-NP	O
Chighsondiowsolalancher	Chighsondiowsolalancher	NNP	I-NP	O
I	I	NNP	I-NP	O
DONT	DONT	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
KNOW	KNOW	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
melz	melz	NN	B-NP	O
@	@	SYM	O	O
mvazquez17	mvazquez17	NN	B-NP	O
Me	me	PRP	O	O
sending	send	VBG	B-VP	O
my	my	PRP$	B-NP	O
dog	dog	NN	I-NP	O
out	out	RP	I-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
supplies	supply	NNS	B-NP	O
since	since	IN	O	O
he	he	PRP	O	O
ca	can	MD	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
contract	contract	VB	B-VP	O
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	B-NP	O
LogoT	LogoT	NNP	I-NP	O
coc	coc	NNP	I-NP	O
GIF	GIF	NNP	I-NP	O
10:04	10:04	CD	I-NP	O
AM	AM	NNP	I-NP	O
-	-	:	O	O
Mar	Mar	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
13	13	CD	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
-	-	:	O	O
Twitter	Twitter	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
iPhone	iPhone	NN	B-NP	O
				
As	as	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
CDC	CDC	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
continaes	continae	VBZ	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
study	study	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
spread	spread	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
,	,	,	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
ecommend	ecommend	VBP	B-VP	O
that	that	IN	B-PP	O
people	people	NNS	B-NP	O
wear	wear	VBP	B-VP	O
cloth	cloth	JJ	B-NP	O
face	face	NN	I-NP	O
coverings	covering	NNS	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
public	public	JJ	B-NP	O
settings	setting	NNS	I-NP	O
where	where	WRB	B-ADVP	O
social	social	JJ	B-NP	O
distancing	distancing	NN	I-NP	O
measures	measure	NNS	I-NP	O
can	can	MD	B-VP	O
be	be	VB	I-VP	O
difficult	difficult	JJ	B-AP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
maintain	maintain	VB	I-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
Remember	Remember	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
,	,	,	O	O
this	this	DT	B-VP	O
does	do	VBZ	I-VP	O
not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
replace	replace	VB	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
importance	importance	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
ocial	ocial	JJ	B-NP	O
distancing	distancing	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Ii	Ii	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
recommended	recommend	VBN	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
koep	koep	VB	I-VP	O
us	us	PRP	O	O
all	all	DT	B-AP	O
safe	safe	JJ	I-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
FLOTUS	FLOTUS	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
Melania	Melania	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
				
TRUMP	TRUMP	NN	B-NP	O
DEFENDS	DEFEND	VBZ	B-VP	O
USE	USE	NN	B-NP	O
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	O
PHRASE	PHRASE	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
'	'	POS	I-NP	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
,	,	,	O	O
DESPITE	DESPITE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
DEMANDS	DEMANDS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
FROM	FROM	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TO	TO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
STOP	STOP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HAS	HAS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NOW	NOW	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
RENAMED	RENAMED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SYPHILIS	SYPHILIS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TRUMP	TRUMP	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
imgflip.com	imgflip.com	NN	I-NP	O
				
Actual	actual	JJ	B-NP	O
footage	footage	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
teachers	teacher	NNS	B-NP	O
if	if	IN	O	O
they	they	PRP	O	O
hear	hear	VBP	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
student	student	NN	I-NP	O
cough	cough	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
their	their	PRP$	B-NP	O
classroom	classroom	NN	I-NP	O
estudentsaywhat	estudentsaywhat	NN	I-NP	O
				
Sour	sour	JJ	B-AP	O
@	@	SYM	O	O
Sour258	sour258	CD	B-NP	O
indian	indian	JJ	I-NP	O
cook	cook	NN	I-NP	O
getting	get	VBG	B-VP	O
boycotted	boycott	VBN	I-VP	O
for	for	IN	B-VP	O
selling	sell	VBG	I-VP	O
indian	indian	JJ	B-NP	O
chinese	chinese	JJ	I-NP	O
gobi	gobi	NN	I-NP	O
manchurian	manchurian	NN	I-NP	O
				
Watching	watch	VBG	B-VP	O
someone	someone	NN	B-NP	O
waste	waste	NN	I-NP	O
Soap	Soap	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Ber	Ber	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Bernie	Bernie	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Watching	Watching	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
someone	someone	NN	I-NP	O
waste	waste	NN	I-NP	O
handwash	handwash	NN	I-NP	O
Watching	watch	VBG	B-VP	O
someone	someone	NN	B-NP	O
Bern	bern	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
waste	waste	NN	I-NP	O
sanitizer	sanitizer	NN	I-NP	O
Watching	watch	VBG	B-VP	O
someone	someone	NN	B-NP	O
waste	waste	NN	I-NP	O
Urrak	Urrak	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Inie	Inie	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Generzy	Generzy	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
ILEO	ILEO	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
ANE	ANE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	I-MISC
A	A	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC
LIE	LIE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
NFD	NFD	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
A	A	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
supporter	supporter	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
California	California	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
holds	hold	VBZ	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
sign	sign	NN	I-NP	O
saying	say	VBG	B-VP	O
COVID-19	COVID-19	NN	B-NP	B-MISC
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	I-MISC
A	A	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC
LIE	LIE	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
while	while	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
mask	mask	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
hazmat	hazmat	NN	B-NP	O
suit	suit	NN	I-NP	O
				
r	r	LS	O	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
MurderedByWords	MurderedByWords	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Trumputin	Trumputin	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
something	something	NN	B-NP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
ship	ship	VBP	B-VP	O
OC	OC	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
6	6	CD	I-NP	O
9	9	CD	I-NP	O
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
6	6	CD	I-NP	O
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
Dr.	Dr.	NNP	I-NP	O
Anthony	Anthony	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Fauci	Fauci	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
unveils	unveil	VBZ	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
mask	mask	NN	I-NP	O
that	that	WDT	B-NP	O
could	can	MD	B-VP	O
save	save	VB	I-VP	O
millions	million	NNS	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
lives	life	NNS	B-NP	O
Politics	Politics	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
Pics	Pics	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
&	&	CC	I-NP	I-ORG
Gifs	Gifs	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HOUSE	HOUSE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
16.4k	16.4k	CD	I-NP	O
I	I	CD	I-NP	O
726	726	CD	I-NP	O
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
Share	Share	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
Award	Award	NNP	I-NP	O
Y	Y	NNP	I-NP	O
BEST	BEST	NNP	I-NP	O
COMMENTS	COMMENTS	NNP	I-NP	O
▼	▼	NN	I-NP	O
香2Awards	香2Award	NNS	I-NP	O
Why	why	WRB	B-ADVP	O
does	do	VBZ	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
he	he	PRP	O	O
just	just	RB	B-ADVP	O
wear	wear	VBP	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
ball	ball	NN	I-NP	O
gag	gag	NN	I-NP	O
he	he	PRP	O	O
uses	use	VBZ	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
Putin	Putin	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
?	?	.	O	O
				
1	1	CD	B-NP	O
538	538	CD	I-NP	O
11	11	CD	I-NP	O
Share	Share	NNP	I-NP	O
O	O	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Award	Award	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
I	I	PRP	O	O
hate	hate	VBP	B-VP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
r	r	NN	B-NP	O
/	/	SYM	O	O
murderedbywords	murderedbyword	NNS	B-NP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
burning	burn	VBG	I-NP	O
passion	passion	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
HAHA	HAHA	NNP	B-NP	O
tRuMp	tRuMp	NNP	I-NP	O
=	=	SYM	O	O
gAy	gAy	NNP	B-NP	O
fOr	fOr	IN	B-PP	O
PuTIN	PuTIN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
WEARS	WEAR	VBZ	B-VP	O
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
MASK	MASK	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SAME	SAME	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WAY	WAY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
EXIT	EXIT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HE	HE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HANDLES	HANDLES	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
PANDEMIC	PANDEMIC	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
makeameme.org	makeameme.org	NN	I-NP	O
				
GOD	GOD	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
DAM	DAM	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CARL	CARL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
THERE	THERE	EX	O	O
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	O
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
MUCH	MUCH	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
MORE	MORE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SINISTER	SINISTER	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
REASON	REASON	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WHY	WHY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LET	LET	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
GO	GO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
AND	AND	CC	O	I-ORG
WITHHELD	WITHHELD	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
INFORMATION	INFORMATION	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
.	.	.	O	O
				
AS	AS	IN	B-PP	O
PELOSI	PELOSI	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
SAID.CHINA	SAID.CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
PREFERS	PREFERS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BIDEN	BIDEN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
WIN	WIN	VB	I-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
ELECTION	ELECTION	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
WHERE	WHERE	WRB	B-ADVP	O
'S	'S	POS	B-NP	O
HUNTER	HUNTER	NNP	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
WILL	WILL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
HUNTER	HUNTER	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BE	BE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SUICIDED	SUICIDED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LIKE	LIKE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
EPSTEIN	EPSTEIN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
?	?	.	O	O
imgflip.com	imgflip.com	NN	B-NP	O
				
Doctor	Doctor	NNP	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
used	use	VBD	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
destroy	destroy	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
Oh	oh	UH	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
Was	be	VBD	B-VP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
Speeding	speed	VBG	B-VP	O
Officer	officer	NN	B-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
?	?	.	O	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
Wuhan	Wuhan	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
are	be	VBP	B-VP	O
wondering	wonder	VBG	I-VP	O
why	why	WRB	B-ADVP	O
there	there	EX	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
only	only	RB	B-NP	O
1	1	CD	I-NP	O
plane	plane	NN	I-NP	O
coming	come	VBG	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
disinfect	disinfect	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
city	city	NN	I-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
Exterminates	Exterminates	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
in	in	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
Wuhan	Wuhan	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
(	(	(	O	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
)	)	)	O	O
				
FIRST	FIRST	NNP	B-NP	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
GOT	GOT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CORONA	CORONA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NOW	NOW	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
US	US	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
LETS	LETS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
GO	GO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
KILLED	KILL	VBN	B-VP	O
BY	BY	IN	B-PP	O
ALCOHOL	ALCOHOL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
&	&	CC	I-NP	I-ORG
TEMPERATURES	TEMPERATURES	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
ABOVE	ABOVE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
57	57	CD	I-NP	O
DEGREES	DEGREES	NNS	I-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
Donald	Donald	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Trump	Trump	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Jr.	Jr.	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
•	•	SYM	O	O
..	..	:	O	O
IGGER	IGGER	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
June	June	NNP	I-NP	O
30	30	CD	I-NP	O
at	at	IN	B-PP	O
5:35	5:35	CD	B-NP	O
PM	PM	NNP	I-NP	O
·	·	NNP	I-NP	O
Solid	Solid	NNP	I-NP	O
point	point	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
what	what	WP	B-NP	O
virologist	virologist	NN	I-NP	O
wear	wear	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
protect	protect	VB	I-VP	O
themselves	themselves	PRP	O	O
from	from	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
worry	worry	VB	B-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
though	though	RB	B-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
bandana	bandana	NN	I-NP	O
probably	probably	RB	B-ADVP	O
works	work	VBZ	B-VP	O
,	,	,	O	O
too	too	RB	B-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Chinese	Chinese	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC
woman	woman	NN	I-NP	O
dodges	dodge	VBZ	B-VP	O
airport	airport	NN	B-NP	O
screening	screening	NN	I-NP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
France	France	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
travellers	traveller	NNS	B-NP	O
told	tell	VBD	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
heed	heed	VB	I-VP	O
checks	check	NNS	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
Wuhan	Wuhan	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
What	what	WP	B-NP	O
an	an	DT	B-NP	O
idiot	idiot	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
What	what	WP	B-NP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Idiotic	idiotic	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
idiot	idiot	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
dude	dude	NN	I-NP	O
sneezes	sneeze	VBZ	B-VP	O
right	right	RB	B-AP	O
next	next	JJ	I-AP	O
to	to	TO	O	O
yOU	yOU	PRP	O	O
@	@	IN	B-PP	O
mcb	mcb	NN	B-NP	O
Mr.	Mr.	NNP	I-NP	O
Stark	Stark	NNP	I-NP	O
...	...	:	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
feel	feel	VB	B-VP	O
so	so	RB	B-AP	O
good	good	JJ	I-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
wanna	wanna	VB	B-VP	O
go	go	VB	I-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Mr.	Mr.	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Stark	Stark	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
,	,	,	O	O
please	please	VB	B-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Say	say	VB	B-VP	O
hello	hello	NN	B-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
46th	46th	JJ	I-NP	O
president	president	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Doe	Doe	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Exotic	Exotic	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
AW	AW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
GEEZ	GEEZ	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IT	IT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
'S	'S	POS	I-NP	I-ORG
NOT	NOT	RB	I-NP	I-ORG
LIKE	LIKE	IN	O	I-ORG
HE	HE	PRP	O	I-ORG
CALLED	CALL	VBD	B-VP	I-ORG
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINK	CHINK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
were	be	VBD	B-VP	O
about	about	IN	O	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
finish	finish	VB	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-AP	O
long	long	JJ	I-AP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
annoying	annoy	VBG	B-VP	O
task	task	NN	B-NP	O
but	but	CC	O	O
then	then	RB	B-ADVP	O
some	some	DT	B-NP	O
jerk	jerk	NN	I-NP	O
reports	report	VBZ	B-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
dead	dead	JJ	I-NP	O
body	body	NN	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Memezila.com	Memezila.com	NNP	B-NP	O
				
DEMOCRATS	DEMOCRATS	NNS	B-NP	O
WENEED	WENE	VBD	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
LOCKDOWN	LOCKDOWN	NNP	B-NP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
SAVE	SAVE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
LIVESI	LIVESI	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
WHAT	WHAT	WP	B-NP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
LOCKDOWNS	LOCKDOWNS	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG
ARE	ARE	VBP	B-VP	I-ORG
DOING	DO	VBG	I-VP	I-ORG
So	so	RB	B-NP	I-ORG
130	130	CD	I-NP	O
Million	million	CD	I-NP	B-MISC
People	people	NNS	I-NP	I-MISC
Could	can	MD	B-VP	I-MISC
Starve	starve	VB	I-VP	I-MISC
Because	because	IN	O	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
Lockdowns	Lockdowns	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
NEWS	NEWS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
COVID	COVID	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
could	can	MD	B-VP	O
push	push	VB	I-VP	O
265	265	CD	B-NP	O
million	million	CD	I-NP	O
people	people	NNS	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
starvation	starvation	NN	B-NP	O
if	if	IN	B-PP	O
action	action	NN	B-NP	O
not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
taken	take	VBN	B-VP	O
:	:	:	O	O
UN	UN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
COVID-19	COVID-19	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Linked	Linked	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Hunger	Hunger	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Cauld	Cauld	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Cause	Cause	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
More	More	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Deaths	Deaths	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Than	than	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
The	the	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
Disease	Disease	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Itself	Itself	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
New	New	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Report	Report	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
Finds	Find	NNPS	I-NP	O
I	I	PRP	O	O
CALL	CALL	VBP	B-VP	B-MISC
THAT	THAT	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
EMPATHY	EMPATHY	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
,	,	,	O	O
AND	AND	CC	O	O
COMPASSION	COMPASSION	NN	B-NP	O
				
HOW	HOW	WRB	B-ADVP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-PP	O
AVOID	AVOID	NNP	B-NP	O
UR	UR	NNP	I-NP	O
ANNOYING	ANNOYING	NNP	I-NP	O
RELATIVES	RELATIVES	NNP	I-NP	O
THIS	THIS	NNP	I-NP	O
CNY	CNY	NNP	I-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
POST	POST	NN	B-NP	O
ON	ON	IN	B-PP	O
FB-JUST	FB-JUST	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
BACKFROM	BACKFROM	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
WUHAN	WUHAN	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
				
It	it	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	O	O
your	your	PRP$	B-AP	O
own	own	JJ	I-AP	O
good	good	JJ	I-AP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
You	you	PRP	O	O
've	have	VBP	B-VP	O
got	get	VBN	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
stop	stop	VB	I-VP	O
touching	touch	VBG	I-VP	O
your	your	PRP$	B-NP	O
face	face	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
P.	P.	NN	B-NP	B-PER
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
JUST	JUST	RB	B-ADVP	O
WANT	WANT	VBP	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
SAY	SAY	VB	I-VP	O
ONE	ONE	CD	B-NP	O
THING	THING	NN	I-NP	O
ABOUT	ABOUT	IN	B-PP	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
THIS	THIS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
LONGEST	LONG	JJS	I-NP	I-ORG
SOMETHING	SOMETHING	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
MADE	MADE	VBN	B-VP	I-ORG
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
HAS	HA	VBZ	B-VP	I-ORG
EVER	EVER	RB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
LASTED	LAST	VBN	B-VP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
catch	catch	VBP	B-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
China	China	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
but	but	CC	O	O
you	you	PRP	O	O
already	already	RB	B-ADVP	O
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
AIDS	AIDS	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC
.	.	.	O	O
				
Let	let	VB	B-VP	O
them	them	PRP	O	O
fight	fight	VB	B-VP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
impostor	impostor	NN	I-NP	O
pretending	pretend	VBG	B-VP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
fix	fix	VB	I-VP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
sabotage	sabotage	NN	I-NP	O
he	he	PRP	O	O
did	do	VBD	B-VP	O
3	3	CD	B-NP	O
seconds	second	NNS	I-NP	O
ago	ago	IN	I-NP	O
				
CORONA	CORONA	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
?	?	.	O	O
				
JUST	JUST	RB	B-ADVP	O
CALLIT	CALLIT	VB	B-VP	B-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
THAT	THAT	WDT	B-NP	O
'S	'	VBZ	B-VP	O
WHERE	WHERE	WRB	B-ADVP	O
IT	IT	NNP	B-NP	O
CAME	CAME	NNP	I-NP	O
FROM	FROM	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
WHEN	WHEN	WRB	B-ADVP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	B-NP	O
DONT	DONT	NNP	I-NP	O
HAVE	HAVE	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
PS4	PS4	NNP	I-NP	O
BUT	BUT	NNP	I-NP	O
STILL	STILL	NNP	I-NP	O
GETS	GET	VBZ	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
PLAY	PLAY	VB	I-VP	O
BIOHAZARD	BIOHAZARD	NN	B-NP	O
8	8	CD	I-NP	O
				
ME	ME	PRP	O	O
,	,	,	O	O
TRYING	TRY	VBG	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
DO	DO	VB	I-VP	O
ANYTHING	ANYTHING	NN	B-NP	O
ON	ON	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
INTERNET	INTERNET	NN	I-NP	O
ARE	ARE	VBP	B-VP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
REGISTERED	REGISTER	VBN	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
VOTE	VOTE	VB	I-VP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
1720,1820,and	1720,1820,and	CD	B-NP	O
1920	1920	CD	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
Have	have	VB	B-VP	O
massive	massive	JJ	B-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
outbreaks	outbreak	NNS	I-NP	O
joking	joke	VBG	B-VP	O
about	about	IN	B-PP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
plague	plague	NN	I-NP	O
happening	happen	VBG	B-VP	O
Not	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
even	even	RB	I-ADVP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
month	month	NN	I-NP	O
into	into	IN	B-PP	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
's	's	POS	I-NP	O
'	'	``	O	O
myaterious	myaterious	JJ	B-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
outbreak	outbreak	NN	I-NP	O
grows	grow	VBZ	B-VP	O
with	with	IN	B-PP	O
139	139	CD	B-NP	O
cases	case	NNS	I-NP	O
reported	report	VBN	B-VP	O
over	over	IN	B-NP	O
two	two	CD	I-NP	O
days	day	NNS	I-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
disease	disease	NN	I-NP	O
starts	start	VBZ	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
china	china	NN	B-NP	O
Im	Im	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
beginning	beginning	NN	I-NP	O
to	to	TO	B-VP	O
see	see	VB	I-VP	O
a	a	DT	B-NP	O
patternhere	patternhere	NN	I-NP	O
that	that	IN	O	O
in	in	IN	O	O
nat	nat	FW	O	O
ne	ne	FW	O	O
aure	aure	FW	O	O
i	i	FW	O	O
like	like	IN	O	O
				
As	as	IN	B-PP	O
coronavirus	coronavirus	NN	B-NP	O
cases	case	NNS	I-NP	O
spike	spike	VBP	B-VP	O
worldwide	worldwide	JJ	B-AP	O
,	,	,	O	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
is	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
closing	close	VBG	I-VP	O
itself	itself	PRP	O	O
off	off	RP	O	O
By	by	IN	B-PP	O
James	James	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
Grifmths	Grifmths	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
,	,	,	O	O
CNN	CNN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
Updated	Updated	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
9:15	9:15	CD	I-NP	O
AM	AM	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
EDT	EDT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
,	,	,	O	O
Fri	Fri	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
March	March	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
27	27	CD	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
You	you	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
about	about	IN	O	O
..	..	.	O	O
frve	frve	JJ	B-NP	O
years	year	NNS	I-NP	O
too	too	RB	B-ADVP	O
late	late	RB	I-ADVP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
USA	USA	NNP	B-NP	O
Never	Never	NNP	I-NP	O
Ask	Ask	NNP	I-NP	O
A	A	NNP	I-NP	O
Woman	Woman	NNP	I-NP	O
WE	WE	NNP	I-NP	O
HAVE	HAVE	NNP	I-NP	O
THE	THE	NNP	I-NP	O
HIGHEST	HIGHEST	NNP	I-NP	O
AMOUNT	AMOUNT	NNP	I-NP	O
Her	Her	NNP	I-NP	O
Age	Age	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	I-MISC
COVIDIS	COVIDIS	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC
CASES	CASES	NNS	I-NP	O
IN	IN	IN	B-PP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
WORLD	WORLD	NN	I-NP	B-MISC
A	A	DT	B-NP	I-MISC
Man	man	NN	I-NP	I-MISC
,	,	,	O	O
CHINA	CHINA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
His	His	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Salary	Salary	NNP	I-NP	O
The	The	NNP	I-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Government	Government	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
,	,	,	O	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
HAVE	HAVE	VBP	B-VP	O
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	O
HIGHEST	HIGH	JJS	I-NP	O
AMOUNT	AMOUNT	NN	I-NP	O
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	O
REPORTED	REPORT	VBN	B-NP	O
CASES	CASES	NNS	I-NP	O
The	the	DT	O	O
of	of	IN	O	O
po	po	FW	B-NP	O
wecd	wecd	FW	I-NP	O
wh	wh	FW	I-NP	O
Caronevi	Caronevi	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
				
best	good	JJS	B-NP	O
candidate	candidate	NN	I-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-PP	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
joe	joe	NN	I-NP	O
biden	biden	NN	I-NP	O
Kamala	Kamala	NNP	I-NP	O
harris	harris	NNP	I-NP	O
Bernie	Bernie	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
sanders	sander	NNS	I-NP	O
TIKTO	TIKTO	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
Deliguthrie	Deliguthrie	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
do	do	VBP	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	I-VP	O
know	know	VB	B-VP	O
what	what	WP	B-NP	O
ya	ya	PRP	O	O
got	get	VBD	B-VP	O
til	til	IN	O	O
it	it	PRP	O	O
's	be	VBZ	B-VP	O
gone	go	VBN	I-VP	O
WAFFLE	WAFFLE	NNP	B-NP	O
HOUSE	HOUSE	NNP	I-NP	O
RALE	RALE	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
OUSE	OUSE	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
				
REAKING	REAK	VBG	B-VP	B-ORG
NEWS	NEWS	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG
BLOW	BLOW	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
JOBS	JOBS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
KILL	KILL	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
FECTED	FECTED	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
PERSON	PERSON	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
HAS	HAS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
SYMPTOMS	SYMPTOMS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
an	an	DT	B-NP	O
NBA	NBA	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
LEGEND	LEGEND	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
KOBE	KOBE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
BRYAN	BRYAN	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
NEWw	NEWw	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
				
*	*	SYM	O	O
A	A	DT	B-NP	O
new	new	JJ	I-NP	O
lethal	lethal	JJ	I-NP	O
virus	virus	NN	I-NP	O
starts	start	VBZ	B-VP	O
spreading	spread	VBG	I-VP	O
*	*	SYM	O	O
|	|	SYM	O	O
Africa	Africa	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
no	no	UH	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
What	what	WP	B-NP	O
?	?	.	O	O
				
Sorry	sorry	NN	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
Force	force	NN	B-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
habit	habit	NN	B-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
,	,	,	O	O
no	no	DT	O	O
!	!	.	O	O
nam	nam	NN	B-NP	O
				
When	when	WRB	B-ADVP	O
died	die	VBD	B-VP	O
due	due	JJ	B-AP	O
to	to	TO	B-PP	O
Corona	Corona	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
you	you	PRP	B-NP	O
Virus	Virus	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC
and	and	CC	O	O
again	again	RB	B-ADVP	O
born	bear	VBN	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
				
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
Chinese	Chinese	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
Coronavirus	Coronavirus	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Kung	Kung	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
Flu	Flu	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
				
Citizens	Citizen	NNPS	B-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
You	you	PRP	O	O
ca	can	MD	B-VP	O
n't	not	RB	B-ADVP	O
just	just	RB	I-ADVP	O
let	let	VB	B-VP	O
us	us	PRP	O	O
die	die	VB	B-VP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
The	the	DT	B-NP	O
Government	Government	NNP	I-NP	O
:	:	:	O	O
This	this	DT	B-VP	O
is	be	VBZ	I-VP	O
America	America	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
boredpanda.com	boredpanda.com	NNP	I-NP	O
				
ACTUAL	ACTUAL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
FOOTAGE	FOOTAGE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Teachar	Teachar	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Tech	Tech	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
Time.com	Time.com	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
tru	tru	NN	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
OF	OF	IN	B-PP	O
TEACHERS	TEACHERS	NNS	B-NP	O
TRYING	TRY	VBG	B-VP	O
TO	TO	TO	B-VP	O
GET	GET	VB	I-VP	O
THROUGH	THROUGH	IN	B-PP	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
				
STOP	STOP	VB	B-VP	O
PARANOIA	PARANOIA	NNP	B-NP	O
				
HOW	HOW	WRB	B-ADVP	O
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	O
THINK	THINK	VBP	B-VP	B-ORG
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	I-ORG
LOOK	LOOK	VB	B-VP	I-ORG
PROTESTING	PROTEST	VBG	I-VP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
LOCKDOWNS	LOCKDOWNS	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG
HOW	HOW	WRB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
YOU	YOU	PRP	O	I-ORG
ACTUALLY	ACTUALLY	RB	B-ADVP	I-ORG
LOOK	LOOK	VB	B-VP	I-ORG
PROTESTING	PROTEST	VBG	I-VP	I-ORG
THE	THE	DT	B-NP	I-ORG
LOCKDOWNS	LOCKDOWNS	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG
HELP	HELP	VBP	B-VP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
HELP	HELP	NN	B-NP	O
!	!	.	O	O
				
I	I	PRP	O	O
'M	'M	VBP	B-VP	B-ORG
BEING	BE	VBG	I-VP	I-ORG
REPRESSED	REPRESS	VBN	I-VP	I-ORG
!	!	.	O	O
				
TAKING	TAK	VBG	B-VP	O
CORONAVIRUS	CORONAVIRUS	NNP	B-NP	O
SERIOUSLY	SERIOUSLY	NNP	I-NP	O
USTENING	USTENING	NNP	I-NP	O
TO	TO	NNP	I-NP	O
PUBLIC	PUBLIC	NNP	I-NP	O
HEALTH	HEALTH	NNP	I-NP	O
EXPERTS	EXPERTS	NNP	I-NP	B-PER
GOLF	GOLF	NNP	I-NP	I-PER
AND	AND	CC	O	O
CAMPAIGN	CAMPAIGN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
RALLIES	RALLIES	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG
				
KNIGHT	KNIGHT	NN	B-NP	O
IS	I	VBZ	B-VP	O
BACK	BACK	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
HIT	HIT	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
TV	TV	NN	I-NP	I-ORG
FOR	FOR	IN	B-PP	O
REVENGE	REVENGE	NNP	B-NP	O
WEDNESDAY	WEDNESDAY	NNP	I-NP	O
.	.	.	O	O
				
JANUARY	JANUARY	NNP	B-NP	B-PER
29	29	CD	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
2020	2020	CD	B-NP	O
$	$	$	I-NP	O
1.90	1.90	CD	I-NP	O
HERALDSUN.COM	HERALDSUN.COM	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
AU	AU	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
We	we	PRP	O	O
're	be	VBP	B-VP	O
foryou	foryou	IN	B-PP	O
Minister	Minister	NNP	B-NP	O
slams	slam	VBZ	B-VP	O
schools	school	NNS	B-NP	O
for	for	IN	B-VP	O
turning	turn	VBG	I-VP	O
ldren	ldren	NNS	B-NP	O
away	away	RB	B-NP	O
CORONA	CORONA	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG
CHAOS	CHAOS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
CHINESE	CHINESE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
VIRUS	VIRUS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
PANDAMONIUM	PANDAMONIUM	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
fearful	fearful	JJ	B-AP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
ASHLEY	ASHLEY	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC
ARGOON	ARGOON	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC
AND	AND	CC	O	O
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
been	be	VBN	I-VP	O
GRANT	GRANT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG
MCARTHUR	MCARTHUR	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG
advice	advice	NN	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
tly	tly	RB	B-ADVP	O
visi	visi	VBP	B-VP	O
-	-	:	O	O
and	and	CC	O	O
infectious	infectious	JJ	B-NP	O
di	dus	NNS	I-NP	O
VICTORIAN	VICTORIAN	JJ	I-NP	B-MISC
sch.	sch.	NN	I-NP	O
deadly	deadly	JJ	I-NP	O
coronaviru	coronaviru	NN	I-NP	O
,	,	,	O	O
slammed	slam	VBD	B-VP	O
for	for	IN	B-VP	O
defying	defy	VBG	I-VP	O
m	m	NN	B-NP	O
banning	ban	VBG	B-VP	O
healthy	healthy	JJ	B-NP	O
kids	kid	NNS	I-NP	O
wh	wh	WDT	B-NP	O
ted	t	VBD	B-VP	O
China	China	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
from	from	IN	B-VP	O
retuming	retume	VBG	I-VP	O
to	to	TO	O	O
At	at	IN	B-PP	O
least	least	JJS	B-NP	O
15	15	CD	I-NP	O
schools	school	NNS	I-NP	O
and	and	CC	O	O
kinderga	kinderga	NN	B-NP	O
have	have	VBP	B-VP	O
ordered	order	VBN	I-VP	O
families	family	NNS	B-NP	O
who	who	WP	B-NP	O
bolidayed	boliday	VBD	B-VP	O
in	in	IN	B-PP	O
the	the	DT	B-NP	O
outbreak	outbreak	JJ	I-NP	O
city	city	NN	I-NP	O
of	of	IN	B-PP	O
Wuhan.	Wuhan.	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC
or	or	CC	O	O
any	any	DT	B-VP	O
said	say	VBD	I-VP	O
Any	any	DT	B-NP	O
advice	advice	NN	I-NP	O
that	that	WDT	B-NP	O
contradicts	contradict	VBZ	B-VP	O
this	this	DT	B-ADVP	O
where	where	WRB	I-ADVP	O
